[
    {
        "Front": "あっ",
        "Back": "Ah!,Oh!",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "愛",
        "Back": "love",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 0
    },
    {
        "Front": "挨拶",
        "Back": "greeting,salutation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1
    },
    {
        "Front": "愛情",
        "Back": "love,affection",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2
    },
    {
        "Front": "合図",
        "Back": "sign,signal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3
    },
    {
        "Front": "アイスクリーム",
        "Back": "ice cream",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "愛する",
        "Back": "to love",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 4
    },
    {
        "Front": "相手",
        "Back": "companion,partner,company",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 5
    },
    {
        "Front": "あいにく",
        "Back": "unfortunately,Sorry, but....",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アイロン",
        "Back": "(electric) iron",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アウト",
        "Back": "out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "明かり",
        "Back": "lamplight,light (in general),brightness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 6
    },
    {
        "Front": "空き",
        "Back": "room,time to spare,emptiness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 7
    },
    {
        "Front": "明らか",
        "Back": "obvious,evident,clear",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 8
    },
    {
        "Front": "諦める",
        "Back": "to give up,to abandon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 9
    },
    {
        "Front": "飽きる",
        "Back": "to get tired of,to lose interest in,to have enough",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 10
    },
    {
        "Front": "握手",
        "Back": "handshake",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 11
    },
    {
        "Front": "悪魔",
        "Back": "devil,demon,evil spirit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 12
    },
    {
        "Front": "明ける",
        "Back": "to dawn,to become daylight",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 13
    },
    {
        "Front": "あした",
        "Back": "tomorrow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "預ける",
        "Back": "to give into custody,to entrust,to deposit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 14
    },
    {
        "Front": "汗",
        "Back": "sweat,perspiration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 15
    },
    {
        "Front": "与える",
        "Back": "to give,to present,to award",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 16
    },
    {
        "Front": "暖かい",
        "Back": "warm,mild",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 17
    },
    {
        "Front": "辺り",
        "Back": "vicinity,nearby",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 18
    },
    {
        "Front": "当たる",
        "Back": "to be hit,to be successful,to be equivalent to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 19
    },
    {
        "Front": "あちこち",
        "Back": "here and there",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "扱う",
        "Back": "to handle,to deal with,to treat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 20
    },
    {
        "Front": "集まり",
        "Back": "gathering,meeting,assembly,collection",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 21
    },
    {
        "Front": "当てる",
        "Back": "to hit,to apply a patch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 22
    },
    {
        "Front": "跡",
        "Back": "(1) trace,tracks,mark,sign,(2) remains,ruins,(3) scar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 23
    },
    {
        "Front": "あと",
        "Back": "(1) trace,tracks,(2) remains,ruins,(3) scar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "穴",
        "Back": "hole",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 24
    },
    {
        "Front": "浴びる",
        "Back": "to bathe,to bask in the sun,to shower",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 25
    },
    {
        "Front": "油",
        "Back": "oil",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 26
    },
    {
        "Front": "余り",
        "Back": "not very (used as adverb),not much",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 27
    },
    {
        "Front": "誤り",
        "Back": "error",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 28
    },
    {
        "Front": "粗",
        "Back": "defect,flaw,blemish,weak point",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 29
    },
    {
        "Front": "嵐",
        "Back": "storm,tempest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 30
    },
    {
        "Front": "新た",
        "Back": "new,fresh,novel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 31
    },
    {
        "Front": "あらゆる",
        "Back": "all,every",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "表す",
        "Back": "to express,to show,to reveal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 32
    },
    {
        "Front": "現す",
        "Back": "to show,to indicate,to display",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 33
    },
    {
        "Front": "現れ",
        "Back": "embodiment,materialization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 34
    },
    {
        "Front": "現れる",
        "Back": "(1) to appear,to come in sight,to become visible,(2) to express oneself",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 35
    },
    {
        "Front": "ありがとう",
        "Back": "(conj,exp,int) Thank you",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "有る",
        "Back": "to be,to have",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 36
    },
    {
        "Front": "或",
        "Back": "a certain...,some...",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 37
    },
    {
        "Front": "あるいは",
        "Back": "or,possibly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アルバム",
        "Back": "album",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "泡",
        "Back": "bubble,foam,froth,head on beer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 38
    },
    {
        "Front": "合わせる",
        "Back": "to join together,to be opposite,to face,to unite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 39
    },
    {
        "Front": "哀れ",
        "Back": "helpless,pity,sorrow,grief",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 40
    },
    {
        "Front": "案",
        "Back": "plan,suffix meaning draft",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 41
    },
    {
        "Front": "暗記",
        "Back": "memorization,learning by heart",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 42
    },
    {
        "Front": "安定",
        "Back": "stability,equilibrium",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 43
    },
    {
        "Front": "案内",
        "Back": "information,guidance,leading",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 44
    },
    {
        "Front": "あんなに",
        "Back": "to that extent,to that degree",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "あんまり",
        "Back": "not very,not much,remainder,rest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "胃",
        "Back": "stomach",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 45
    },
    {
        "Front": "いい",
        "Back": "good",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "よい",
        "Back": "good,nice,pleasant,ok",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "いえ",
        "Back": "TODO same as いいえ?",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "委員",
        "Back": "committee member",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 47
    },
    {
        "Front": "言う",
        "Back": "to say",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 48
    },
    {
        "Front": "意外",
        "Back": "unexpected,surprising",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 49
    },
    {
        "Front": "行き",
        "Back": "going",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 50
    },
    {
        "Front": "息",
        "Back": "breath,tone",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 51
    },
    {
        "Front": "勢い",
        "Back": "force,vigor,energy,spirit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 52
    },
    {
        "Front": "生き物",
        "Back": "living thing,animal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 53
    },
    {
        "Front": "幾つ",
        "Back": "how many?,how old?",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 54
    },
    {
        "Front": "幾ら",
        "Back": "how much?,how many?",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 55
    },
    {
        "Front": "いけない",
        "Back": "must not do,bad,wrong,not good",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "医師",
        "Back": "doctor,physician",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 56
    },
    {
        "Front": "意思",
        "Back": "intention,purpose",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 57
    },
    {
        "Front": "意志",
        "Back": "will,volition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 58
    },
    {
        "Front": "維持",
        "Back": "maintenance,preservation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 59
    },
    {
        "Front": "意識",
        "Back": "consciousness,senses",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 60
    },
    {
        "Front": "異常",
        "Back": "strangeness,abnormality,disorder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 61
    },
    {
        "Front": "椅子",
        "Back": "chair",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 62
    },
    {
        "Front": "泉",
        "Back": "spring,fountain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 63
    },
    {
        "Front": "いずれ",
        "Back": "where,which,who",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "以前",
        "Back": "ago,since,before,previous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 64
    },
    {
        "Front": "板",
        "Back": "board,plank",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 65
    },
    {
        "Front": "偉大",
        "Back": "greatness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 66
    },
    {
        "Front": "抱く",
        "Back": "(sl) to embrace,to hug,to harbour,to entertain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 67
    },
    {
        "Front": "いたずら",
        "Back": "tease,prank,trick,practical joke",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "いただきます",
        "Back": "expression of gratitude before meals",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "頂く",
        "Back": "to receive,to take food or drink (hum)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 68
    },
    {
        "Front": "痛み",
        "Back": "pain,ache,sore,grief,distress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 69
    },
    {
        "Front": "至る",
        "Back": "to come,to arrive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 70
    },
    {
        "Front": "いち",
        "Back": "market,fair",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "位置",
        "Back": "place,situation,position,location",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 71
    },
    {
        "Front": "一時",
        "Back": "moment,time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 72
    },
    {
        "Front": "一度に",
        "Back": "all at once",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 73
    },
    {
        "Front": "市場",
        "Back": "(the) market (as a concept)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 74
    },
    {
        "Front": "一番",
        "Back": "best,first,number one",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 75
    },
    {
        "Front": "いつか",
        "Back": "sometime,someday,one day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "一家",
        "Back": "a house,a home,a family,a household",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 76
    },
    {
        "Front": "一種",
        "Back": "a species,a kind,a variety",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 77
    },
    {
        "Front": "一瞬",
        "Back": "a moment,an instant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 78
    },
    {
        "Front": "一生",
        "Back": "whole life,a lifetime,all through life",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 79
    },
    {
        "Front": "一層",
        "Back": "much more,still more,all the more",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 80
    },
    {
        "Front": "一体",
        "Back": "(1) one object,one body,(2) what on earth?,really?,(3) generally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 81
    },
    {
        "Front": "一致",
        "Back": "(1) coincidence,agreement,(2) conformity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 82
    },
    {
        "Front": "いつでも",
        "Back": "(at) any time,always,at all times,never (neg)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "一般",
        "Back": "general,liberal,universal,ordinary,average",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 83
    },
    {
        "Front": "一方",
        "Back": "(1) on the other hand,(2) meanwhile,(3) only,simple,in turn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 84
    },
    {
        "Front": "いつまでも",
        "Back": "forever,for good,eternally,as long as one likes,indefinitely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "いつも",
        "Back": "always,usually,every time,never (with neg. verb)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "移動",
        "Back": "removal,migration,movement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 86
    },
    {
        "Front": "従兄弟",
        "Back": "cousin (male)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 87
    },
    {
        "Front": "稲",
        "Back": "rice-plant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 88
    },
    {
        "Front": "居眠り",
        "Back": "dozing,nodding off",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 89
    },
    {
        "Front": "命",
        "Back": "command,decree,life,destiny",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 90
    },
    {
        "Front": "違反",
        "Back": "violation (of law),transgression,infringement,breach",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 91
    },
    {
        "Front": "衣服",
        "Back": "clothes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 92
    },
    {
        "Front": "居間",
        "Back": "living room (western style)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 93
    },
    {
        "Front": "今に",
        "Back": "before long,even now",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 94
    },
    {
        "Front": "今にも",
        "Back": "at any time,soon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 95
    },
    {
        "Front": "否",
        "Back": "no,the noes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 96
    },
    {
        "Front": "以来",
        "Back": "since,henceforth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 97
    },
    {
        "Front": "依頼",
        "Back": "(1) request,commission,dispatch,(2) dependence,trust",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 98
    },
    {
        "Front": "いらいら",
        "Back": "getting nervous,irritation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "いらっしゃい",
        "Back": "welcome",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "医療",
        "Back": "medical care,medical treatment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 99
    },
    {
        "Front": "岩",
        "Back": "rock,crag",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 100
    },
    {
        "Front": "祝い",
        "Back": "celebration,festival",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 101
    },
    {
        "Front": "祝う",
        "Back": "to congratulate,to celebrate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 102
    },
    {
        "Front": "言わば",
        "Back": "so to speak",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 103
    },
    {
        "Front": "いわゆる",
        "Back": "the so-called,so to speak",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "インク",
        "Back": "ink",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "印刷",
        "Back": "printing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 104
    },
    {
        "Front": "印象",
        "Back": "impression",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 105
    },
    {
        "Front": "引退",
        "Back": "retire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 106
    },
    {
        "Front": "引用",
        "Back": "quotation,citation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 107
    },
    {
        "Front": "ウイスキー",
        "Back": "whisky",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "上",
        "Back": "upper,outer,surface",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 108
    },
    {
        "Front": "魚",
        "Back": "fish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 109
    },
    {
        "Front": "うがい",
        "Back": "gargle,rinse mouth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "伺う",
        "Back": "(hon) to visit,to ask,to inquire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 110
    },
    {
        "Front": "受け取る",
        "Back": "to receive,to get,to accept,to take",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 111
    },
    {
        "Front": "動かす",
        "Back": "to move,to shift",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 112
    },
    {
        "Front": "兎",
        "Back": "rabbit,hare,cony",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 113
    },
    {
        "Front": "牛",
        "Back": "cattle,cow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 114
    },
    {
        "Front": "失う",
        "Back": "to lose,to part with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 115
    },
    {
        "Front": "後",
        "Back": "afterwards,since then,in the future",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 116
    },
    {
        "Front": "嘘",
        "Back": "lie,falsehood,incorrect fact,inappropriate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 117
    },
    {
        "Front": "疑う",
        "Back": "to doubt,to distrust,to be suspicious of,to suspect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 118
    },
    {
        "Front": "内",
        "Back": "inside",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 119
    },
    {
        "Front": "宇宙",
        "Back": "universe,cosmos,space",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 120
    },
    {
        "Front": "撃つ",
        "Back": "to attack,to defeat,to destroy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 121
    },
    {
        "Front": "移す",
        "Back": "to remove,to transfer,to infect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 122
    },
    {
        "Front": "訴える",
        "Back": "to sue (a person),to resort to,to appeal to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 123
    },
    {
        "Front": "うなる",
        "Back": "to groan,to moan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "奪う",
        "Back": "to snatch away",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 124
    },
    {
        "Front": "馬",
        "Back": "(1) horse,(2) promoted bishop (shogi)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 125
    },
    {
        "Front": "うまい",
        "Back": "delicious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "生まれ",
        "Back": "birth,birth-place",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 127
    },
    {
        "Front": "梅",
        "Back": "plum,plum-tree,lowest (of a three-tier ranking system)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 128
    },
    {
        "Front": "裏切る",
        "Back": "to betray,to turn traitor to,to double-cross",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 129
    },
    {
        "Front": "うるさい",
        "Back": "noisy,loud,fussy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "嬉しい",
        "Back": "happy,glad,pleasant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 130
    },
    {
        "Front": "売れる",
        "Back": "to be sold",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 131
    },
    {
        "Front": "噂",
        "Back": "rumour,report,gossip,common talk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 132
    },
    {
        "Front": "うん",
        "Back": "fortune,luck",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "運",
        "Back": "fortune,luck",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 134
    },
    {
        "Front": "運転",
        "Back": "operation,motion,driving",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 135
    },
    {
        "Front": "運動",
        "Back": "motion,exercise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 136
    },
    {
        "Front": "柄",
        "Back": "handle,grip",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 137
    },
    {
        "Front": "永遠",
        "Back": "eternity,perpetuity,immortality,permanence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 138
    },
    {
        "Front": "永久",
        "Back": "eternity,perpetuity,immortality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 139
    },
    {
        "Front": "影響",
        "Back": "influence,effect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 140
    },
    {
        "Front": "営業",
        "Back": "business,trade,management",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 141
    },
    {
        "Front": "衛星",
        "Back": "satellite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 142
    },
    {
        "Front": "栄養",
        "Back": "nutrition,nourishment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 143
    },
    {
        "Front": "笑顔",
        "Back": "smiling face",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 144
    },
    {
        "Front": "描く",
        "Back": "to draw,to paint,to sketch,to depict,to describe",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 145
    },
    {
        "Front": "餌",
        "Back": "feed,bait",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 146
    },
    {
        "Front": "エネルギー",
        "Back": "(n) energy (de: Energie)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "得る",
        "Back": "to get,to gain,to win",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 147
    },
    {
        "Front": "円",
        "Back": "circle,money",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 148
    },
    {
        "Front": "延期",
        "Back": "postponement,adjournment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 149
    },
    {
        "Front": "演技",
        "Back": "acting,performance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 150
    },
    {
        "Front": "援助",
        "Back": "assistance,aid,support",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 151
    },
    {
        "Front": "エンジン",
        "Back": "engine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "演説",
        "Back": "speech,address",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 152
    },
    {
        "Front": "演奏",
        "Back": "musical performance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 153
    },
    {
        "Front": "遠慮",
        "Back": "diffidence,restraint,reserve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 154
    },
    {
        "Front": "御",
        "Back": "honourable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 155
    },
    {
        "Front": "老い",
        "Back": "old age,old person,the old,the aged",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 156
    },
    {
        "Front": "追い付く",
        "Back": "to overtake,to catch up (with)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 157
    },
    {
        "Front": "王",
        "Back": "king,ruler,sovereign,monarch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 158
    },
    {
        "Front": "追う",
        "Back": "to chase,to run after",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 159
    },
    {
        "Front": "王様",
        "Back": "king",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 160
    },
    {
        "Front": "王子",
        "Back": "prince",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 161
    },
    {
        "Front": "応じる",
        "Back": "to respond,to satisfy,to accept,to comply with,to apply for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 162
    },
    {
        "Front": "横断",
        "Back": "crossing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 163
    },
    {
        "Front": "終える",
        "Back": "to finish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 164
    },
    {
        "Front": "大いに",
        "Back": "very,much,greatly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 165
    },
    {
        "Front": "覆う",
        "Back": "to cover,to hide,to conceal,to wrap,to disguise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 166
    },
    {
        "Front": "オーバー",
        "Back": "(1) overcoat,(2) over",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "大家",
        "Back": "rich family,distinguished family",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 167
    },
    {
        "Front": "丘",
        "Back": "hill,height,knoll,rising ground",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 168
    },
    {
        "Front": "沖",
        "Back": "open sea",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 169
    },
    {
        "Front": "奥",
        "Back": "interior,inner part",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 170
    },
    {
        "Front": "贈る",
        "Back": "to send,to give to,to award to,to confer on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 171
    },
    {
        "Front": "起こる",
        "Back": "to occur,to happen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 172
    },
    {
        "Front": "幼い",
        "Back": "very young,childish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 173
    },
    {
        "Front": "収める",
        "Back": "to obtain,to reap,to pay,to supply,to accept",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 174
    },
    {
        "Front": "おじいさん",
        "Back": "grandfather,male senior-citizen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "おしゃべり",
        "Back": "chattering,talk,idle talk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "汚染",
        "Back": "pollution,contamination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 175
    },
    {
        "Front": "おそらく",
        "Back": "perhaps",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "恐れる",
        "Back": "to fear,to be afraid of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 176
    },
    {
        "Front": "恐ろしい",
        "Back": "terrible,dreadful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 177
    },
    {
        "Front": "お互い",
        "Back": "mutual,reciprocal,each other",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 178
    },
    {
        "Front": "穏やか",
        "Back": "calm,gentle,quiet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 179
    },
    {
        "Front": "男の人",
        "Back": "man",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 180
    },
    {
        "Front": "劣る",
        "Back": "to fall behind,to be inferior to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 181
    },
    {
        "Front": "お腹",
        "Back": "stomach",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 182
    },
    {
        "Front": "鬼",
        "Back": "ogre,demon,it (i.e., in a game of tag)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 183
    },
    {
        "Front": "帯",
        "Back": "band (e.g. conduction, valence)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 184
    },
    {
        "Front": "お昼",
        "Back": "lunch,noon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 185
    },
    {
        "Front": "オフィス",
        "Back": "office",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "溺れる",
        "Back": "to be drowned,to indulge in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 186
    },
    {
        "Front": "おまえ",
        "Back": "(fam) you (sing),presence (of a high personage)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "おめでとう",
        "Back": "Congratulations!,an auspicious occasion!",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "お目に掛かる",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 187
    },
    {
        "Front": "思い出",
        "Back": "memories,recollections,reminiscence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 188
    },
    {
        "Front": "主に",
        "Back": "mainly,primarily",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 189
    },
    {
        "Front": "思わず",
        "Back": "unintentional,spontaneous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 190
    },
    {
        "Front": "おや",
        "Back": "parents",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "泳ぎ",
        "Back": "swimming",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 191
    },
    {
        "Front": "およそ",
        "Back": "about,roughly,as a rule,approximately",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "及ぼす",
        "Back": "to exert,to cause,to exercise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 192
    },
    {
        "Front": "居る",
        "Back": "to be (animate),to be,to exist",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 193
    },
    {
        "Front": "下す",
        "Back": "to lower,to let go down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 194
    },
    {
        "Front": "降ろす",
        "Back": "to take down,to launch,to drop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 195
    },
    {
        "Front": "終",
        "Back": "the end",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 196
    },
    {
        "Front": "音",
        "Back": "sound,note",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 197
    },
    {
        "Front": "恩",
        "Back": "favour,obligation,debt of gratitude",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 198
    },
    {
        "Front": "温暖",
        "Back": "warmth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 199
    },
    {
        "Front": "温度",
        "Back": "temperature",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 200
    },
    {
        "Front": "可",
        "Back": "passable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 201
    },
    {
        "Front": "課",
        "Back": "counter for chapters (of a book)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 202
    },
    {
        "Front": "カー",
        "Back": "car",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "カード",
        "Back": "card,curd",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "会",
        "Back": "meeting,assembly,party,association,club",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 203
    },
    {
        "Front": "回",
        "Back": "counter for occurrences",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 204
    },
    {
        "Front": "害",
        "Back": "injury,harm,evil influence,damage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 205
    },
    {
        "Front": "会員",
        "Back": "member,the membership",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 206
    },
    {
        "Front": "絵画",
        "Back": "picture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 207
    },
    {
        "Front": "海外",
        "Back": "foreign,abroad,overseas",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 208
    },
    {
        "Front": "会計",
        "Back": "account,finance,accountant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 209
    },
    {
        "Front": "解決",
        "Back": "settlement,solution,resolution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 210
    },
    {
        "Front": "会合",
        "Back": "meeting,assembly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 211
    },
    {
        "Front": "外交",
        "Back": "diplomacy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 212
    },
    {
        "Front": "開始",
        "Back": "start,commencement,beginning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 213
    },
    {
        "Front": "解釈",
        "Back": "explanation,interpretation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 214
    },
    {
        "Front": "外出",
        "Back": "outing,going out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 215
    },
    {
        "Front": "改善",
        "Back": "betterment,improvement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 216
    },
    {
        "Front": "快適",
        "Back": "pleasant,agreeable,comfortable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 217
    },
    {
        "Front": "回復",
        "Back": "recovery (from illness),improvement,rehabilitation,restoration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 218
    },
    {
        "Front": "飼う",
        "Back": "to keep,to raise,to feed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 219
    },
    {
        "Front": "替える",
        "Back": "to exchange,to interchange,to substitute,to replace",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 220
    },
    {
        "Front": "換える",
        "Back": "to exchange,to interchange,to substitute,to replace",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 221
    },
    {
        "Front": "香り",
        "Back": "aroma,fragrance,scent,smell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 222
    },
    {
        "Front": "画家",
        "Back": "painter,artist",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 223
    },
    {
        "Front": "抱える",
        "Back": "to hold or carry under or in the arms",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 224
    },
    {
        "Front": "価格",
        "Back": "price,value,cost",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 225
    },
    {
        "Front": "化学",
        "Back": "chemistry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 226
    },
    {
        "Front": "輝く",
        "Back": "to shine,to glitter,to sparkle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 227
    },
    {
        "Front": "係",
        "Back": "official,duty,person in charge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 228
    },
    {
        "Front": "掛かる",
        "Back": "to take (e.g. time, money, etc),to hang",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 229
    },
    {
        "Front": "罹る",
        "Back": "to suffer from",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 230
    },
    {
        "Front": "鍵",
        "Back": "key",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 231
    },
    {
        "Front": "限る",
        "Back": "to restrict,to limit,to confine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 232
    },
    {
        "Front": "家具",
        "Back": "furniture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 233
    },
    {
        "Front": "学",
        "Back": "learning,scholarship,erudition,knowledge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 234
    },
    {
        "Front": "額",
        "Back": "forehead,brow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 235
    },
    {
        "Front": "覚悟",
        "Back": "resolution,resignation,readiness,preparedness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 236
    },
    {
        "Front": "確実",
        "Back": "certainty,reliability,soundness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 237
    },
    {
        "Front": "学者",
        "Back": "scholar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 238
    },
    {
        "Front": "学習",
        "Back": "study,learning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 239
    },
    {
        "Front": "隠す",
        "Back": "to hide,to conceal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 240
    },
    {
        "Front": "拡大",
        "Back": "magnification,enlargement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 241
    },
    {
        "Front": "確認",
        "Back": "affirmation,confirmation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 242
    },
    {
        "Front": "学問",
        "Back": "scholarship,study,learning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 243
    },
    {
        "Front": "隠れる",
        "Back": "to hide,to be hidden,to conceal oneself,to disappear",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 244
    },
    {
        "Front": "影",
        "Back": "shade,shadow,other side",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 245
    },
    {
        "Front": "陰",
        "Back": "shade,shadow,other side",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 246
    },
    {
        "Front": "欠ける",
        "Back": "to be lacking",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 247
    },
    {
        "Front": "加減",
        "Back": "addition and subtraction,allowance for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 248
    },
    {
        "Front": "過去",
        "Back": "the past,bygone days,the previous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 249
    },
    {
        "Front": "籠",
        "Back": "basket,cage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 250
    },
    {
        "Front": "囲む",
        "Back": "to surround,to encircle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 251
    },
    {
        "Front": "火災",
        "Back": "conflagration,fire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 252
    },
    {
        "Front": "貸し",
        "Back": "loan,lending",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 253
    },
    {
        "Front": "菓子",
        "Back": "pastry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 254
    },
    {
        "Front": "家事",
        "Back": "housework,domestic chores",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 255
    },
    {
        "Front": "賢い",
        "Back": "wise,clever,smart",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 256
    },
    {
        "Front": "歌手",
        "Back": "singer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 257
    },
    {
        "Front": "数",
        "Back": "number,figure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 258
    },
    {
        "Front": "稼ぐ",
        "Back": "to earn income,to labor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 259
    },
    {
        "Front": "数える",
        "Back": "to count",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 260
    },
    {
        "Front": "型",
        "Back": "mold,model,style,shape,data-type",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 261
    },
    {
        "Front": "肩",
        "Back": "shoulder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 262
    },
    {
        "Front": "硬い",
        "Back": "solid,hard (esp. metal, stone),unpolished writing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 263
    },
    {
        "Front": "方々",
        "Back": "persons,this and that,here and there,everywhere",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 264
    },
    {
        "Front": "刀",
        "Back": "sword,saber,knife,engraving tool",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 265
    },
    {
        "Front": "語る",
        "Back": "to talk,to tell,to recite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 266
    },
    {
        "Front": "勝ち",
        "Back": "win,victory",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 267
    },
    {
        "Front": "価値",
        "Back": "value,worth,merit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 268
    },
    {
        "Front": "がっかり",
        "Back": "feel disappointed,be dejected,lose heart",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "活気",
        "Back": "energy,liveliness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 269
    },
    {
        "Front": "学期",
        "Back": "term (school)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 270
    },
    {
        "Front": "格好",
        "Back": "shape,form,posture,suitability",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 271
    },
    {
        "Front": "活動",
        "Back": "action,activity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 272
    },
    {
        "Front": "活用",
        "Back": "conjugation,practical use",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 273
    },
    {
        "Front": "悲しむ",
        "Back": "to be sad,to mourn for,to regret",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 274
    },
    {
        "Front": "必ずしも",
        "Back": "(not) always,(not) necessarily,(not) all,(not) entirely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 275
    },
    {
        "Front": "かなり",
        "Back": "considerably,fairly,quite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "金",
        "Back": "(1) gold,(2) gold general (shogi) (abbr)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 276
    },
    {
        "Front": "金持ち",
        "Back": "rich man",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 277
    },
    {
        "Front": "可能",
        "Back": "possible,practicable,feasible",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 278
    },
    {
        "Front": "株",
        "Back": "share,stock,stump (of tree)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 279
    },
    {
        "Front": "被る",
        "Back": "to suffer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 280
    },
    {
        "Front": "構う",
        "Back": "to mind,to care about,to be concerned about",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 281
    },
    {
        "Front": "我慢",
        "Back": "patience,endurance,perseverance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 282
    },
    {
        "Front": "神",
        "Back": "god",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 283
    },
    {
        "Front": "雷",
        "Back": "thunder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 284
    },
    {
        "Front": "髪の毛",
        "Back": "hair (head)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 285
    },
    {
        "Front": "科目",
        "Back": "(school) subject,curriculum,course",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 286
    },
    {
        "Front": "かもしれない",
        "Back": "may,might,perhaps,may be,possibly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "火曜",
        "Back": "(abbr) Tuesday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 287
    },
    {
        "Front": "空",
        "Back": "sky",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 288
    },
    {
        "Front": "刈る",
        "Back": "to cut (hair),to mow (grass),to harvest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 289
    },
    {
        "Front": "彼等",
        "Back": "they (usually male)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 290
    },
    {
        "Front": "川",
        "Back": "river",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 291
    },
    {
        "Front": "河",
        "Back": "river,stream",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 292
    },
    {
        "Front": "皮",
        "Back": "skin,hide,leather,fur,pelt,bark,shell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 293
    },
    {
        "Front": "革",
        "Back": "leather",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 294
    },
    {
        "Front": "かわいそう",
        "Back": "poor,pitiable,pathetic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "かわいらしい",
        "Back": "lovely,sweet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "缶",
        "Back": "can,tin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 295
    },
    {
        "Front": "勘",
        "Back": "perception,intuition,the sixth sense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 296
    },
    {
        "Front": "考え",
        "Back": "thinking,thought,ideas,intention",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 297
    },
    {
        "Front": "感覚",
        "Back": "sense,sensation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 298
    },
    {
        "Front": "観客",
        "Back": "audience,spectator(s)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 299
    },
    {
        "Front": "環境",
        "Back": "environment,circumstance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 300
    },
    {
        "Front": "歓迎",
        "Back": "welcome,reception",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 301
    },
    {
        "Front": "観光",
        "Back": "sightseeing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 302
    },
    {
        "Front": "感じ",
        "Back": "feeling,sense,impression",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 304
    },
    {
        "Front": "観察",
        "Back": "observation,survey",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 303
    },
    {
        "Front": "感謝",
        "Back": "thanks,gratitude",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 305
    },
    {
        "Front": "患者",
        "Back": "a patient",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 306
    },
    {
        "Front": "勘定",
        "Back": "calculation,counting,consideration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 307
    },
    {
        "Front": "感情",
        "Back": "emotion(s),feeling(s),sentiment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 308
    },
    {
        "Front": "感じる",
        "Back": "to feel,to sense,to experience",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 309
    },
    {
        "Front": "感心",
        "Back": "admiration,Well done!",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 310
    },
    {
        "Front": "関心",
        "Back": "concern,interest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 311
    },
    {
        "Front": "関する",
        "Back": "to concern,to be related",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 312
    },
    {
        "Front": "完成",
        "Back": "(1) complete,completion,(2) perfection,accomplishment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 313
    },
    {
        "Front": "完全",
        "Back": "perfection,completeness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 314
    },
    {
        "Front": "感動",
        "Back": "being deeply moved,excitement,impression,deep emotion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 315
    },
    {
        "Front": "監督",
        "Back": "supervision,control,superintendence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 316
    },
    {
        "Front": "管理",
        "Back": "control,management (e.g. of a business)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 317
    },
    {
        "Front": "完了",
        "Back": "completion,conclusion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 318
    },
    {
        "Front": "関連",
        "Back": "relation,connection,relevance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 319
    },
    {
        "Front": "議員",
        "Back": "member of the Diet, congress or parliament",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 320
    },
    {
        "Front": "記憶",
        "Back": "memory,recollection,remembrance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 321
    },
    {
        "Front": "気温",
        "Back": "temperature",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 322
    },
    {
        "Front": "機械",
        "Back": "machine,mechanism",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 323
    },
    {
        "Front": "議会",
        "Back": "Diet,congress,parliament",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 324
    },
    {
        "Front": "期間",
        "Back": "period,term",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 325
    },
    {
        "Front": "機関",
        "Back": "organ,mechanism,facility,engine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 326
    },
    {
        "Front": "企業",
        "Back": "enterprise,undertaking",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 327
    },
    {
        "Front": "効く",
        "Back": "to be effective",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 328
    },
    {
        "Front": "機嫌",
        "Back": "humour,temper,mood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 329
    },
    {
        "Front": "気候",
        "Back": "climate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 330
    },
    {
        "Front": "岸",
        "Back": "bank,coast,shore",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 331
    },
    {
        "Front": "生地",
        "Back": "birthplace",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 332
    },
    {
        "Front": "記事",
        "Back": "article,news story,report,account",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 333
    },
    {
        "Front": "技師",
        "Back": "engineer,technician",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 334
    },
    {
        "Front": "記者",
        "Back": "reporter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 335
    },
    {
        "Front": "傷",
        "Back": "wound,injury,hurt,cut",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 336
    },
    {
        "Front": "期待",
        "Back": "expectation,anticipation,hope",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 337
    },
    {
        "Front": "帰宅",
        "Back": "returning home",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 338
    },
    {
        "Front": "貴重",
        "Back": "precious,valuable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 339
    },
    {
        "Front": "議長",
        "Back": "chairman",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 340
    },
    {
        "Front": "きちんと",
        "Back": "precisely,accurately",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "きつい",
        "Back": "tight,close,intense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "気付く",
        "Back": "to notice,to recognize,to become aware of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 341
    },
    {
        "Front": "気に入る",
        "Back": "to be pleased with,to suit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 342
    },
    {
        "Front": "記入",
        "Back": "entry,filling in of forms",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 343
    },
    {
        "Front": "記念",
        "Back": "commemoration,memory",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 344
    },
    {
        "Front": "機能",
        "Back": "function,faculty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 345
    },
    {
        "Front": "気の毒",
        "Back": "pitiful,a pity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 346
    },
    {
        "Front": "寄付",
        "Back": "contribution,donation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 347
    },
    {
        "Front": "希望",
        "Back": "hope,wish,aspiration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 348
    },
    {
        "Front": "基本",
        "Back": "foundation,basis,standard",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 349
    },
    {
        "Front": "決まり",
        "Back": "settlement,conclusion,regulation,rule",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 350
    },
    {
        "Front": "気味",
        "Back": "-like,-looking,-looked",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 351
    },
    {
        "Front": "奇妙",
        "Back": "strange,queer,curious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 353
    },
    {
        "Front": "義務",
        "Back": "duty,obligation,responsibility",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 352
    },
    {
        "Front": "疑問",
        "Back": "question,problem,doubt,guess",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 354
    },
    {
        "Front": "逆",
        "Back": "reverse,opposite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 355
    },
    {
        "Front": "キャプテン",
        "Back": "captain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "キャンプ",
        "Back": "camp",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "九",
        "Back": "nine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 356
    },
    {
        "Front": "旧",
        "Back": "ex-",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 357
    },
    {
        "Front": "級",
        "Back": "class, grade, rank,school class, grade",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 358
    },
    {
        "Front": "球",
        "Back": "globe,sphere,ball",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 359
    },
    {
        "Front": "休暇",
        "Back": "holiday,day off,furlough",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 360
    },
    {
        "Front": "休憩",
        "Back": "rest,break,recess,intermission",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 361
    },
    {
        "Front": "急激",
        "Back": "sudden,precipitous,radical",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 362
    },
    {
        "Front": "吸収",
        "Back": "absorption,suction,attraction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 363
    },
    {
        "Front": "救助",
        "Back": "relief,aid,rescue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 364
    },
    {
        "Front": "急速",
        "Back": "rapid (e.g. progress)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 365
    },
    {
        "Front": "急に",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 366
    },
    {
        "Front": "給料",
        "Back": "salary,wages",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 367
    },
    {
        "Front": "器用",
        "Back": "skillful,handy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 368
    },
    {
        "Front": "教科書",
        "Back": "text book",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 369
    },
    {
        "Front": "競技",
        "Back": "game,match,contest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 370
    },
    {
        "Front": "行儀",
        "Back": "manners",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 371
    },
    {
        "Front": "供給",
        "Back": "supply,provision",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 372
    },
    {
        "Front": "教師",
        "Back": "teacher (classroom)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 373
    },
    {
        "Front": "教授",
        "Back": "teaching,instruction,professor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 374
    },
    {
        "Front": "強調",
        "Back": "emphasis,stress,stressed point",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 375
    },
    {
        "Front": "共通",
        "Back": "commonness,community",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 376
    },
    {
        "Front": "共同",
        "Back": "cooperation,association,collaboration,joint",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 377
    },
    {
        "Front": "恐怖",
        "Back": "be afraid,dread,dismay,terror",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 378
    },
    {
        "Front": "協力",
        "Back": "cooperation,collaboration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 379
    },
    {
        "Front": "強力",
        "Back": "herculean strength,mountain carrier-guide",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 380
    },
    {
        "Front": "許可",
        "Back": "permission,approval",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 381
    },
    {
        "Front": "局",
        "Back": "court lady,lady in waiting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 382
    },
    {
        "Front": "巨大",
        "Back": "huge,gigantic,enormous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 383
    },
    {
        "Front": "嫌う",
        "Back": "to hate,to dislike,to loathe",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 384
    },
    {
        "Front": "霧",
        "Back": "fog,mist",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 385
    },
    {
        "Front": "切れ",
        "Back": "cloth,piece,cut,chop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 386
    },
    {
        "Front": "切れる",
        "Back": "(1) to cut well,to be sharp,(2) to break (off)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 387
    },
    {
        "Front": "キロ",
        "Back": "(abbr) kilo-,kilogram,kilometre,10^3",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "記録",
        "Back": "record,minutes,document",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 388
    },
    {
        "Front": "議論",
        "Back": "argument,discussion,dispute",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 389
    },
    {
        "Front": "銀",
        "Back": "(1) silver,silver coin,silver paint",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 390
    },
    {
        "Front": "禁煙",
        "Back": "No Smoking!",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 391
    },
    {
        "Front": "金額",
        "Back": "amount of money",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 392
    },
    {
        "Front": "金庫",
        "Back": "safe,vault,treasury,provider of funds",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 393
    },
    {
        "Front": "禁止",
        "Back": "prohibition,ban",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 394
    },
    {
        "Front": "金銭",
        "Back": "money,cash",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 395
    },
    {
        "Front": "金属",
        "Back": "metal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 396
    },
    {
        "Front": "近代",
        "Back": "present day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 397
    },
    {
        "Front": "緊張",
        "Back": "tension,mental strain,nervousness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 398
    },
    {
        "Front": "筋肉",
        "Back": "muscle,sinew",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 399
    },
    {
        "Front": "金融",
        "Back": "monetary circulation,credit situation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 400
    },
    {
        "Front": "金曜",
        "Back": "(abbr) Friday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 401
    },
    {
        "Front": "句",
        "Back": "sentence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 402
    },
    {
        "Front": "食う",
        "Back": "(male) (vulg) to eat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 403
    },
    {
        "Front": "偶然",
        "Back": "(by) chance,unexpectedly,suddenly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 404
    },
    {
        "Front": "臭い",
        "Back": "odour,scent,smell,stench",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 405
    },
    {
        "Front": "鎖",
        "Back": "chain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 406
    },
    {
        "Front": "腐る",
        "Back": "to rot,to go bad",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 407
    },
    {
        "Front": "癖",
        "Back": "a habit (often a bad habit),peculiarity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 408
    },
    {
        "Front": "管",
        "Back": "pipe,tube",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 409
    },
    {
        "Front": "具体",
        "Back": "concrete,tangible,material",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 410
    },
    {
        "Front": "下さる",
        "Back": "(hon) to give,to confer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 411
    },
    {
        "Front": "下り",
        "Back": "down-train (going away from Tokyo)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 412
    },
    {
        "Front": "苦痛",
        "Back": "pain,agony",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 413
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぐっすり",
        "Back": "sound asleep,fast asleep",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "区別",
        "Back": "distinction,differentiation,classification",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 414
    },
    {
        "Front": "組",
        "Back": "class,group,team,set",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 415
    },
    {
        "Front": "組合",
        "Back": "association,union",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 416
    },
    {
        "Front": "組む",
        "Back": "to put together",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 417
    },
    {
        "Front": "曇",
        "Back": "cloudiness,cloudy weather,shadow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 418
    },
    {
        "Front": "位",
        "Back": "grade,rank,about",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 419
    },
    {
        "Front": "暮らし",
        "Back": "living,livelihood,subsistence,circumstances",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 420
    },
    {
        "Front": "クラシック",
        "Back": "classic(s)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "暮らす",
        "Back": "to live,to get along",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 421
    },
    {
        "Front": "グラス",
        "Back": "(1) glass,(2) grass",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "グランド",
        "Back": "gland,grand,(electrical) ground",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "クリーム",
        "Back": "cream",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "繰り返す",
        "Back": "to repeat,to do something over again",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 422
    },
    {
        "Front": "クリスマス",
        "Back": "Christmas",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "狂う",
        "Back": "to go mad,to get out of order",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 423
    },
    {
        "Front": "グループ",
        "Back": "group",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "苦しい",
        "Back": "painful,difficult",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 424
    },
    {
        "Front": "苦しむ",
        "Back": "to suffer,to groan,to be worried",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 425
    },
    {
        "Front": "暮れ",
        "Back": "year end,sunset,nightfall,end",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 426
    },
    {
        "Front": "苦労",
        "Back": "troubles,hardships",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 427
    },
    {
        "Front": "加える",
        "Back": "to append,to sum up,to add (up)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 428
    },
    {
        "Front": "詳しい",
        "Back": "knowing very well,detailed,full,accurate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 429
    },
    {
        "Front": "加わる",
        "Back": "to join in,to accede to,to increase,to gain in (influence)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 430
    },
    {
        "Front": "訓",
        "Back": "native Japanese reading of a Chinese character",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 431
    },
    {
        "Front": "軍",
        "Back": "army,force,troops",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 432
    },
    {
        "Front": "軍隊",
        "Back": "army,troops",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 433
    },
    {
        "Front": "訓練",
        "Back": "practice,training",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 434
    },
    {
        "Front": "下",
        "Back": "under,below,beneath",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 435
    },
    {
        "Front": "計",
        "Back": "plan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 436
    },
    {
        "Front": "敬意",
        "Back": "respect,honour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 437
    },
    {
        "Front": "経営",
        "Back": "management,administration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 438
    },
    {
        "Front": "計画",
        "Back": "plan,project,schedule,scheme,program",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 439
    },
    {
        "Front": "景気",
        "Back": "condition,state,business (condition)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 440
    },
    {
        "Front": "経験",
        "Back": "experience",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 441
    },
    {
        "Front": "傾向",
        "Back": "tendency,trend,inclination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 442
    },
    {
        "Front": "警告",
        "Back": "warning,advice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 443
    },
    {
        "Front": "計算",
        "Back": "calculation,reckoning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 444
    },
    {
        "Front": "掲示",
        "Back": "notice,bulletin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 445
    },
    {
        "Front": "刑事",
        "Back": "criminal case,(police) detective",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 446
    },
    {
        "Front": "芸術",
        "Back": "(fine) art,the arts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 447
    },
    {
        "Front": "契約",
        "Back": "contract,compact,agreement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 448
    },
    {
        "Front": "経由",
        "Back": "go by the way,via",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 449
    },
    {
        "Front": "ケース",
        "Back": "case",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ゲーム",
        "Back": "game",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "怪我",
        "Back": "injury (to animate object),hurt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 450
    },
    {
        "Front": "劇",
        "Back": "drama,play",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 451
    },
    {
        "Front": "劇場",
        "Back": "theatre,playhouse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 452
    },
    {
        "Front": "化粧",
        "Back": "make-up (cosmetic)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 453
    },
    {
        "Front": "けち",
        "Back": "stinginess,miser,miserliness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "結果",
        "Back": "result,consequence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 454
    },
    {
        "Front": "欠陥",
        "Back": "defect,fault,deficiency",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 455
    },
    {
        "Front": "結局",
        "Back": "after all,eventually",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 456
    },
    {
        "Front": "決心",
        "Back": "determination,resolution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 457
    },
    {
        "Front": "欠席",
        "Back": "absence,non-attendance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 458
    },
    {
        "Front": "決定",
        "Back": "decision,determination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 459
    },
    {
        "Front": "欠点",
        "Back": "faults,defect,weakness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 460
    },
    {
        "Front": "月曜",
        "Back": "Monday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 461
    },
    {
        "Front": "結論",
        "Back": "conclusion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 462
    },
    {
        "Front": "煙",
        "Back": "smoke,fumes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 463
    },
    {
        "Front": "券",
        "Back": "ticket,coupon,bond,certificate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 464
    },
    {
        "Front": "県",
        "Back": "prefecture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 465
    },
    {
        "Front": "軒",
        "Back": "eaves",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 466
    },
    {
        "Front": "喧嘩",
        "Back": "quarrel,(drunken) brawl,failure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 467
    },
    {
        "Front": "見解",
        "Back": "opinion,point of view",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 468
    },
    {
        "Front": "限界",
        "Back": "limit,bound",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 469
    },
    {
        "Front": "現金",
        "Back": "cash,ready money,mercenary,self-interested",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 470
    },
    {
        "Front": "言語",
        "Back": "language",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 471
    },
    {
        "Front": "健康",
        "Back": "health,sound,wholesome",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 472
    },
    {
        "Front": "検査",
        "Back": "inspection (e.g. customs, factory),examination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 473
    },
    {
        "Front": "現在",
        "Back": "present,up to now,nowadays,modern times,current",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 474
    },
    {
        "Front": "現実",
        "Back": "reality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 475
    },
    {
        "Front": "現象",
        "Back": "phenomenon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 476
    },
    {
        "Front": "現状",
        "Back": "present condition,existing state,status quo",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 477
    },
    {
        "Front": "建設",
        "Back": "construction,establishment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 478
    },
    {
        "Front": "現代",
        "Back": "nowadays,modern times,present-day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 479
    },
    {
        "Front": "建築",
        "Back": "construction,architecture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 480
    },
    {
        "Front": "見当",
        "Back": "be found,aim,estimate,guess,approx",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 481
    },
    {
        "Front": "検討",
        "Back": "consideration,examination,investigation,study,scrutiny",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 482
    },
    {
        "Front": "現場",
        "Back": "actual spot,scene,scene of the crime",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 483
    },
    {
        "Front": "憲法",
        "Back": "constitution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 484
    },
    {
        "Front": "権利",
        "Back": "right,privilege",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 485
    },
    {
        "Front": "語",
        "Back": "language,word",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 486
    },
    {
        "Front": "恋",
        "Back": "love,tender passion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 487
    },
    {
        "Front": "濃い",
        "Back": "thick (as of color, liquid),dense,strong",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 488
    },
    {
        "Front": "恋人",
        "Back": "lover,sweetheart",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 489
    },
    {
        "Front": "幸運",
        "Back": "good luck,fortune",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 490
    },
    {
        "Front": "講演",
        "Back": "lecture,address",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 491
    },
    {
        "Front": "効果",
        "Back": "effect,effectiveness,efficacy,result",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 492
    },
    {
        "Front": "硬貨",
        "Back": "coin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 493
    },
    {
        "Front": "高価",
        "Back": "high price",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 494
    },
    {
        "Front": "豪華",
        "Back": "wonderful,gorgeous,splendor,pomp,extravagance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 495
    },
    {
        "Front": "合格",
        "Back": "success,passing (e.g. exam),eligibility",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 496
    },
    {
        "Front": "交換",
        "Back": "exchange,interchange,reciprocity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 497
    },
    {
        "Front": "航空",
        "Back": "aviation,flying",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 498
    },
    {
        "Front": "光景",
        "Back": "scene,spectacle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 499
    },
    {
        "Front": "合計",
        "Back": "sum total,total amount",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 500
    },
    {
        "Front": "攻撃",
        "Back": "attack,strike,offensive,criticism,censure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 501
    },
    {
        "Front": "貢献",
        "Back": "contribution,services",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 502
    },
    {
        "Front": "広告",
        "Back": "advertisement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 503
    },
    {
        "Front": "交際",
        "Back": "company,friendship,association,society,acquaintance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 504
    },
    {
        "Front": "後者",
        "Back": "the latter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 505
    },
    {
        "Front": "工場",
        "Back": "factory,plant,mill,workshop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 506
    },
    {
        "Front": "構成",
        "Back": "organization,composition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 507
    },
    {
        "Front": "高速",
        "Back": "high speed,high gear",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 508
    },
    {
        "Front": "行動",
        "Back": "action,conduct,behaviour,mobilization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 509
    },
    {
        "Front": "強盗",
        "Back": "robbery,burglary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 510
    },
    {
        "Front": "幸福",
        "Back": "happiness,blessedness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 511
    },
    {
        "Front": "公平",
        "Back": "fairness,impartial,justice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 512
    },
    {
        "Front": "候補",
        "Back": "candidacy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 513
    },
    {
        "Front": "考慮",
        "Back": "consideration,taking into account",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 514
    },
    {
        "Front": "越える",
        "Back": "to exceed,to cross over,to cross",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 515
    },
    {
        "Front": "コーチ",
        "Back": "coach",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "コード",
        "Back": "code,cord,chord",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "氷",
        "Back": "ice,hail",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 516
    },
    {
        "Front": "凍る",
        "Back": "to freeze,to be frozen over,to congeal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 517
    },
    {
        "Front": "ゴール",
        "Back": "goal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "誤解",
        "Back": "misunderstanding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 518
    },
    {
        "Front": "語学",
        "Back": "language study",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 519
    },
    {
        "Front": "呼吸",
        "Back": "breath,respiration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 520
    },
    {
        "Front": "故郷",
        "Back": "home town,birthplace,old village,historic village",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 521
    },
    {
        "Front": "極",
        "Back": "quite,very",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 522
    },
    {
        "Front": "国語",
        "Back": "national language",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 523
    },
    {
        "Front": "黒板",
        "Back": "blackboard",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 524
    },
    {
        "Front": "克服",
        "Back": "subjugation,conquest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 525
    },
    {
        "Front": "国民",
        "Back": "national,people,citizen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 526
    },
    {
        "Front": "穀物",
        "Back": "grain,cereal,corn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 527
    },
    {
        "Front": "ここ",
        "Back": "here",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "腰",
        "Back": "hip",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 529
    },
    {
        "Front": "故障",
        "Back": "break-down,failure,accident,out of order",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 530
    },
    {
        "Front": "個人",
        "Back": "individual,private person,personal,private",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 531
    },
    {
        "Front": "越す",
        "Back": "to go over (e.g. with audience)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 532
    },
    {
        "Front": "国家",
        "Back": "state,country,nation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 533
    },
    {
        "Front": "国会",
        "Back": "National Diet,parliament,congress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 534
    },
    {
        "Front": "国境",
        "Back": "national or state border",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 535
    },
    {
        "Front": "骨折",
        "Back": "bone fracture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 536
    },
    {
        "Front": "小包",
        "Back": "parcel,package",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 537
    },
    {
        "Front": "事",
        "Back": "thing,matter,fact,circumstances",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 538
    },
    {
        "Front": "異なる",
        "Back": "to differ,to vary,to disagree",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 539
    },
    {
        "Front": "諺",
        "Back": "proverb,maxim",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 540
    },
    {
        "Front": "断る",
        "Back": "to refuse,to decline,to dismiss",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 541
    },
    {
        "Front": "粉",
        "Back": "flour,meal,powder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 542
    },
    {
        "Front": "この",
        "Back": "this",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "好み",
        "Back": "liking,taste,choice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 544
    },
    {
        "Front": "好む",
        "Back": "to like,to prefer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 545
    },
    {
        "Front": "コピー",
        "Back": "(1) a (photo)copy,(2) blurb on a book jacket",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "塵",
        "Back": "dust,dirt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 546
    },
    {
        "Front": "小麦",
        "Back": "wheat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 547
    },
    {
        "Front": "ごめんなさい",
        "Back": "I beg your pardon,excuse me",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "小屋",
        "Back": "hut,cabin,shed,(animal) pen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 548
    },
    {
        "Front": "これら",
        "Back": "these",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "頃",
        "Back": "time,about,toward,approximately (time)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 549
    },
    {
        "Front": "殺す",
        "Back": "to kill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 550
    },
    {
        "Front": "転ぶ",
        "Back": "to fall down,to fall over",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 551
    },
    {
        "Front": "今回",
        "Back": "now,this time,lately",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 552
    },
    {
        "Front": "今後",
        "Back": "from now on,hereafter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 553
    },
    {
        "Front": "混雑",
        "Back": "confusion,congestion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 554
    },
    {
        "Front": "こんなに",
        "Back": "so,like this,in this way",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "困難",
        "Back": "difficulty,distress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 555
    },
    {
        "Front": "今日",
        "Back": "today,this day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 556
    },
    {
        "Front": "こんにちは",
        "Back": "hello,good day (daytime greeting, id)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "コンピューター",
        "Back": "computer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "婚約",
        "Back": "engagement,betrothal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 557
    },
    {
        "Front": "混乱",
        "Back": "disorder,chaos,confusion,mayhem",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 558
    },
    {
        "Front": "差",
        "Back": "difference,variation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 559
    },
    {
        "Front": "サービス",
        "Back": "(1) service,support system,(2) goods or services without charge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "際",
        "Back": "on the occasion of,circumstances",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 560
    },
    {
        "Front": "最高",
        "Back": "highest,supreme,the most",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 561
    },
    {
        "Front": "財産",
        "Back": "property,fortune,assets",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 562
    },
    {
        "Front": "最終",
        "Back": "last,final,closing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 563
    },
    {
        "Front": "最中",
        "Back": "in the middle of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 564
    },
    {
        "Front": "最低",
        "Back": "least,lowest,worst",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 565
    },
    {
        "Front": "才能",
        "Back": "talent,ability",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 566
    },
    {
        "Front": "裁判",
        "Back": "trial,judgement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 567
    },
    {
        "Front": "材料",
        "Back": "ingredients,material",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 568
    },
    {
        "Front": "幸い",
        "Back": "happiness,blessedness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 569
    },
    {
        "Front": "サイン",
        "Back": "(1) autograph,(2) sign,(3) sine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "境",
        "Back": "border,boundary,mental state",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 570
    },
    {
        "Front": "逆らう",
        "Back": "to go against,to oppose,to disobey,to defy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 571
    },
    {
        "Front": "盛り",
        "Back": "helping,serving",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 572
    },
    {
        "Front": "作業",
        "Back": "work,operation,manufacturing,fatigue duty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 573
    },
    {
        "Front": "昨",
        "Back": "last (year),yesterday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 574
    },
    {
        "Front": "作品",
        "Back": "work,opus,performance,production",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 575
    },
    {
        "Front": "作物",
        "Back": "produce (e.g. agricultural),crops",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 576
    },
    {
        "Front": "桜",
        "Back": "cherry blossom,cherry tree",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 577
    },
    {
        "Front": "酒",
        "Back": "alcohol,sake",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 578
    },
    {
        "Front": "叫ぶ",
        "Back": "to shout,to cry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 579
    },
    {
        "Front": "避ける",
        "Back": "(1) to avoid (physical contact ),(2) to ward off,to avert",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 580
    },
    {
        "Front": "支える",
        "Back": "to be blocked,to choke,to be obstructed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 581
    },
    {
        "Front": "指す",
        "Back": "to point,to put up umbrella,to play",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 582
    },
    {
        "Front": "座席",
        "Back": "seat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 583
    },
    {
        "Front": "誘う",
        "Back": "(1) to invite,to ask,(2) to tempt,to lure,to induce",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 584
    },
    {
        "Front": "札",
        "Back": "(1) token,label,(2) ticket,(3) charm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 585
    },
    {
        "Front": "作家",
        "Back": "author,writer,novelist,artist",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 586
    },
    {
        "Front": "作曲",
        "Back": "composition,setting (of music)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 587
    },
    {
        "Front": "ざっと",
        "Back": "roughly,in round numbers",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "さっぱり",
        "Back": "feeling refreshed,feeling relieved,neat,trimmed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "さて",
        "Back": "well,now,then",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "砂漠",
        "Back": "desert",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 588
    },
    {
        "Front": "差別",
        "Back": "discrimination,distinction,differentiation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 589
    },
    {
        "Front": "作法",
        "Back": "manners,etiquette,propriety",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 590
    },
    {
        "Front": "様々",
        "Back": "varied,various",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 591
    },
    {
        "Front": "覚ます",
        "Back": "to awaken",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 592
    },
    {
        "Front": "覚める",
        "Back": "to wake,to wake up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 593
    },
    {
        "Front": "左右",
        "Back": "(1) left and right,(2) influence,control,domination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 594
    },
    {
        "Front": "皿",
        "Back": "plate,dish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 595
    },
    {
        "Front": "更に",
        "Back": "furthermore,again,after all,more and more,moreover",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 596
    },
    {
        "Front": "去る",
        "Back": "to leave,to go away",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 597
    },
    {
        "Front": "猿",
        "Back": "monkey",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 598
    },
    {
        "Front": "騒ぎ",
        "Back": "uproar,disturbance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 599
    },
    {
        "Front": "参加",
        "Back": "participation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 600
    },
    {
        "Front": "参考",
        "Back": "reference,consultation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 601
    },
    {
        "Front": "賛成",
        "Back": "approval,agreement,support,favour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 602
    },
    {
        "Front": "酸素",
        "Back": "oxygen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 603
    },
    {
        "Front": "散歩",
        "Back": "walk,stroll",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 604
    },
    {
        "Front": "四",
        "Back": "four",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 605
    },
    {
        "Front": "氏",
        "Back": "family name,lineage,birth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 606
    },
    {
        "Front": "詩",
        "Back": "poem,verse of poetry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 607
    },
    {
        "Front": "幸せ",
        "Back": "happiness,good fortune,luck,blessing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 608
    },
    {
        "Front": "ジーンズ",
        "Back": "jeans",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ジェット機",
        "Back": "jet aeroplane",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 609
    },
    {
        "Front": "直に",
        "Back": "immediately,readily,directly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 610
    },
    {
        "Front": "しかも",
        "Back": "moreover,furthermore,nevertheless,and yet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "叱る",
        "Back": "to scold",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 611
    },
    {
        "Front": "式",
        "Back": "equation,formula,ceremony",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 612
    },
    {
        "Front": "直",
        "Back": "earnestly,immediately,exactly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 613
    },
    {
        "Front": "時期",
        "Back": "time,season,period",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 614
    },
    {
        "Front": "支給",
        "Back": "payment,allowance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 615
    },
    {
        "Front": "しきりに",
        "Back": "frequently,repeatedly,incessantly,eagerly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "刺激",
        "Back": "stimulus,impetus,incentive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 616
    },
    {
        "Front": "資源",
        "Back": "resources",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 617
    },
    {
        "Front": "事件",
        "Back": "event,affair,incident",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 618
    },
    {
        "Front": "時刻",
        "Back": "instant,time,moment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 619
    },
    {
        "Front": "自殺",
        "Back": "suicide",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 620
    },
    {
        "Front": "事実",
        "Back": "fact,truth,reality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 621
    },
    {
        "Front": "支出",
        "Back": "expenditure,expenses",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 622
    },
    {
        "Front": "事情",
        "Back": "circumstances,consideration,conditions,situation,reasons",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 623
    },
    {
        "Front": "詩人",
        "Back": "poet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 624
    },
    {
        "Front": "自身",
        "Back": "by oneself,personally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 625
    },
    {
        "Front": "沈む",
        "Back": "to sink,to feel depressed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 626
    },
    {
        "Front": "自然",
        "Back": "nature,spontaneous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 627
    },
    {
        "Front": "思想",
        "Back": "thought,idea",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 628
    },
    {
        "Front": "舌",
        "Back": "tongue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 629
    },
    {
        "Front": "次第",
        "Back": "(1) order,precedence,(2) circumstances,(3) immediate(ly)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 630
    },
    {
        "Front": "事態",
        "Back": "situation,present state of affairs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 631
    },
    {
        "Front": "従う",
        "Back": "to abide (by the rules),to obey,to follow,to accompany",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 632
    },
    {
        "Front": "したがって",
        "Back": "therefore,consequently,in accordance with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "支度",
        "Back": "preparation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 634
    },
    {
        "Front": "親しい",
        "Back": "intimate,close (e.g. friend)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 635
    },
    {
        "Front": "七",
        "Back": "seven",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 636
    },
    {
        "Front": "質",
        "Back": "quality,nature (of person)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 637
    },
    {
        "Front": "失業",
        "Back": "unemployment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 638
    },
    {
        "Front": "実験",
        "Back": "experiment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 639
    },
    {
        "Front": "実現",
        "Back": "implementation,materialization,realization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 640
    },
    {
        "Front": "実行",
        "Back": "practice,performance,execution (e.g. program),realization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 641
    },
    {
        "Front": "実際",
        "Back": "practical,actual condition,status quo",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 642
    },
    {
        "Front": "実施",
        "Back": "enforcement,enact,put into practice,carry out,operation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 643
    },
    {
        "Front": "じっと",
        "Back": "fixedly,firmly,patiently,quietly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "実に",
        "Back": "indeed,truly,surely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 644
    },
    {
        "Front": "実は",
        "Back": "as a matter of fact,by the way",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 645
    },
    {
        "Front": "失望",
        "Back": "disappointment,despair",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 646
    },
    {
        "Front": "支店",
        "Back": "branch store (office)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 647
    },
    {
        "Front": "指導",
        "Back": "leadership,guidance,coaching",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 648
    },
    {
        "Front": "自動",
        "Back": "automatic,self-motion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 649
    },
    {
        "Front": "品",
        "Back": "thing,article,goods,dignity,article (goods),counter for meal courses",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 650
    },
    {
        "Front": "支配",
        "Back": "rule,control,direction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 651
    },
    {
        "Front": "芝居",
        "Back": "play,drama",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 652
    },
    {
        "Front": "しばしば",
        "Back": "often,again and again,frequently",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "芝生",
        "Back": "lawn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 653
    },
    {
        "Front": "支払",
        "Back": "payment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 654
    },
    {
        "Front": "支払う",
        "Back": "to pay",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 655
    },
    {
        "Front": "死亡",
        "Back": "death,mortality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 656
    },
    {
        "Front": "資本",
        "Back": "funds,capital",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 657
    },
    {
        "Front": "しまい",
        "Back": "sisters",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "姉妹",
        "Back": "sisters",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 659
    },
    {
        "Front": "しまう",
        "Back": "to finish,to close,to do something completely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "しまった",
        "Back": "Damn it!",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "自慢",
        "Back": "pride,boast",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 662
    },
    {
        "Front": "事務",
        "Back": "business,office work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 663
    },
    {
        "Front": "示す",
        "Back": "to denote,to show,to point out,to indicate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 664
    },
    {
        "Front": "占める",
        "Back": "(1) to comprise,to account for,to make up (of),(2) to hold,to occupy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 665
    },
    {
        "Front": "霜",
        "Back": "frost",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 666
    },
    {
        "Front": "じゃあ",
        "Back": "well,well then",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "借金",
        "Back": "debt,loan,liabilities",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 667
    },
    {
        "Front": "しゃべる",
        "Back": "to talk,to chat,to chatter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "邪魔",
        "Back": "hindrance,intrusion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 668
    },
    {
        "Front": "週",
        "Back": "week",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 669
    },
    {
        "Front": "州",
        "Back": "sandbank",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 670
    },
    {
        "Front": "十",
        "Back": "10,ten",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 671
    },
    {
        "Front": "銃",
        "Back": "gun",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 672
    },
    {
        "Front": "周囲",
        "Back": "surroundings,circumference,environs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 673
    },
    {
        "Front": "収穫",
        "Back": "harvest,crop,ingathering",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 674
    },
    {
        "Front": "週間",
        "Back": "week,weekly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 675
    },
    {
        "Front": "宗教",
        "Back": "religion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 676
    },
    {
        "Front": "重視",
        "Back": "importance,stress,serious consideration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 677
    },
    {
        "Front": "就職",
        "Back": "finding employment,inauguration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 678
    },
    {
        "Front": "ジュース",
        "Back": "juice,soft drink,deuce",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "修正",
        "Back": "amendment,correction,revision,modification",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 679
    },
    {
        "Front": "渋滞",
        "Back": "congestion (e.g. traffic),delay,stagnation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 680
    },
    {
        "Front": "重大",
        "Back": "serious,important,grave,weighty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 681
    },
    {
        "Front": "住宅",
        "Back": "resident,housing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 682
    },
    {
        "Front": "集団",
        "Back": "group,mass",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 683
    },
    {
        "Front": "集中",
        "Back": "concentration,focusing the mind",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 684
    },
    {
        "Front": "収入",
        "Back": "income,receipts,revenue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 685
    },
    {
        "Front": "住民",
        "Back": "citizens,inhabitants,residents,population",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 686
    },
    {
        "Front": "重要",
        "Back": "important,momentous,essential,principal,major",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 687
    },
    {
        "Front": "修理",
        "Back": "repairing,mending",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 688
    },
    {
        "Front": "主義",
        "Back": "doctrine,rule,principle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 689
    },
    {
        "Front": "宿泊",
        "Back": "lodging",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 690
    },
    {
        "Front": "手術",
        "Back": "surgical operation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 691
    },
    {
        "Front": "首相",
        "Back": "Prime Minister",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 692
    },
    {
        "Front": "手段",
        "Back": "means,way,measure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 693
    },
    {
        "Front": "主張",
        "Back": "claim,request,insistence,assertion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 694
    },
    {
        "Front": "出身",
        "Back": "graduate from,come from",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 695
    },
    {
        "Front": "出席",
        "Back": "attendance,presence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 696
    },
    {
        "Front": "出発",
        "Back": "departure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 697
    },
    {
        "Front": "出版",
        "Back": "publication",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 698
    },
    {
        "Front": "首都",
        "Back": "capital city",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 699
    },
    {
        "Front": "主婦",
        "Back": "housewife,mistress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 700
    },
    {
        "Front": "主要",
        "Back": "chief,main,principal,major",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 701
    },
    {
        "Front": "需要",
        "Back": "demand,request",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 702
    },
    {
        "Front": "種類",
        "Back": "variety,kind,type",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 703
    },
    {
        "Front": "順",
        "Back": "order,turn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 704
    },
    {
        "Front": "瞬間",
        "Back": "moment,second,instant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 705
    },
    {
        "Front": "順調",
        "Back": "favourable,doing well,O.K.,all right",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 706
    },
    {
        "Front": "順番",
        "Back": "turn (in line),order of things",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 707
    },
    {
        "Front": "準備",
        "Back": "preparation,arrangements,provision,reserve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 708
    },
    {
        "Front": "使用",
        "Back": "use,application,employment,utilization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 709
    },
    {
        "Front": "小",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 710
    },
    {
        "Front": "章",
        "Back": "(1) chapter,section,(2) medal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 711
    },
    {
        "Front": "賞",
        "Back": "prize,award",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 712
    },
    {
        "Front": "障害",
        "Back": "obstacle,impediment (fault),damage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 713
    },
    {
        "Front": "奨学金",
        "Back": "scholarship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 714
    },
    {
        "Front": "乗客",
        "Back": "passenger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 715
    },
    {
        "Front": "上京",
        "Back": "proceeding to the capital (Tokyo)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 716
    },
    {
        "Front": "状況",
        "Back": "state of affairs,situation,circumstances",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 717
    },
    {
        "Front": "条件",
        "Back": "conditions,terms",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 718
    },
    {
        "Front": "正午",
        "Back": "noon,mid-day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 719
    },
    {
        "Front": "正直",
        "Back": "honesty,integrity,frankness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 720
    },
    {
        "Front": "常識",
        "Back": "common sense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 721
    },
    {
        "Front": "少女",
        "Back": "daughter,young lady,virgin,maiden,little girl",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 722
    },
    {
        "Front": "少々",
        "Back": "just a minute,small quantity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 723
    },
    {
        "Front": "症状",
        "Back": "symptoms,condition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 724
    },
    {
        "Front": "生じる",
        "Back": "to produce,to yield,to result from,to arise,to be generated",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 725
    },
    {
        "Front": "招待",
        "Back": "invitation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 726
    },
    {
        "Front": "状態",
        "Back": "condition,situation,circumstances,state",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 727
    },
    {
        "Front": "上達",
        "Back": "improvement,advance,progress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 728
    },
    {
        "Front": "冗談",
        "Back": "jest,joke",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 729
    },
    {
        "Front": "承知",
        "Back": "consent,acceptance,assent,admitting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 730
    },
    {
        "Front": "上等",
        "Back": "superiority,first class,very good",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 731
    },
    {
        "Front": "衝突",
        "Back": "collision,conflict",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 732
    },
    {
        "Front": "商人",
        "Back": "trader,shopkeeper,merchant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 733
    },
    {
        "Front": "承認",
        "Back": "recognition,acknowledgement,approval,consent,agreement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 734
    },
    {
        "Front": "少年",
        "Back": "boys,juveniles",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 735
    },
    {
        "Front": "商売",
        "Back": "trade,business,commerce,transaction,occupation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 736
    },
    {
        "Front": "消費",
        "Back": "consumption,expenditure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 737
    },
    {
        "Front": "商品",
        "Back": "commodity,article of commerce,goods,stock,merchandise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 738
    },
    {
        "Front": "消防",
        "Back": "fire fighting,fire department",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 739
    },
    {
        "Front": "情報",
        "Back": "information,(military) intelligence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 740
    },
    {
        "Front": "証明",
        "Back": "proof,verification",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 741
    },
    {
        "Front": "女王",
        "Back": "queen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 742
    },
    {
        "Front": "職",
        "Back": "employment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 743
    },
    {
        "Front": "職業",
        "Back": "occupation,business",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 744
    },
    {
        "Front": "食事",
        "Back": "meal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 745
    },
    {
        "Front": "食卓",
        "Back": "dining table",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 746
    },
    {
        "Front": "食品",
        "Back": "commodity,foodstuff",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 747
    },
    {
        "Front": "植物",
        "Back": "plant,vegetation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 748
    },
    {
        "Front": "食物",
        "Back": "food,foodstuff",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 749
    },
    {
        "Front": "食欲",
        "Back": "appetite (for food)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 750
    },
    {
        "Front": "食料",
        "Back": "food",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 751
    },
    {
        "Front": "食糧",
        "Back": "provisions,rations",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 752
    },
    {
        "Front": "書斎",
        "Back": "study",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 753
    },
    {
        "Front": "女子",
        "Back": "woman,girl",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 754
    },
    {
        "Front": "助手",
        "Back": "helper,helpmeet,assistant,tutor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 755
    },
    {
        "Front": "徐々に",
        "Back": "slowly,little by little,gradually,steadily,quietly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 756
    },
    {
        "Front": "署名",
        "Back": "signature",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 757
    },
    {
        "Front": "書物",
        "Back": "books",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 758
    },
    {
        "Front": "女優",
        "Back": "actress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 759
    },
    {
        "Front": "処理",
        "Back": "processing,dealing with,treatment,disposition,disposal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 760
    },
    {
        "Front": "書類",
        "Back": "documents,official papers",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 761
    },
    {
        "Front": "知らせ",
        "Back": "notice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 762
    },
    {
        "Front": "尻",
        "Back": "buttocks,bottom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 763
    },
    {
        "Front": "印",
        "Back": "(1) mark,(2) symbol,(3) evidence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 764
    },
    {
        "Front": "城",
        "Back": "castle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 765
    },
    {
        "Front": "進学",
        "Back": "going on to university",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 766
    },
    {
        "Front": "神経",
        "Back": "nerve,sensitivity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 767
    },
    {
        "Front": "真剣",
        "Back": "seriousness,earnestness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 768
    },
    {
        "Front": "信仰",
        "Back": "(religious) faith,belief,creed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 769
    },
    {
        "Front": "信号",
        "Back": "traffic lights,signal,semaphore",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 770
    },
    {
        "Front": "人工",
        "Back": "artificial,manmade,human work,human skill,artificiality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 771
    },
    {
        "Front": "深刻",
        "Back": "serious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 772
    },
    {
        "Front": "診察",
        "Back": "medical examination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 773
    },
    {
        "Front": "人種",
        "Back": "race (of people)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 774
    },
    {
        "Front": "信じる",
        "Back": "to believe,to place trust in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 775
    },
    {
        "Front": "人生",
        "Back": "(human) life (i.e. conception to death)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 776
    },
    {
        "Front": "親戚",
        "Back": "relative",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 777
    },
    {
        "Front": "新鮮",
        "Back": "fresh",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 778
    },
    {
        "Front": "心臓",
        "Back": "heart",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 779
    },
    {
        "Front": "身体",
        "Back": "the body",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 780
    },
    {
        "Front": "身長",
        "Back": "height (of body),stature",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 781
    },
    {
        "Front": "慎重",
        "Back": "discretion,prudence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 782
    },
    {
        "Front": "心配",
        "Back": "worry,concern,anxiety,care",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 783
    },
    {
        "Front": "審判",
        "Back": "refereeing,trial,judgement,umpire,referee",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 784
    },
    {
        "Front": "人物",
        "Back": "character,personality,person,man,personage,talented man",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 785
    },
    {
        "Front": "進歩",
        "Back": "progress,development",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 786
    },
    {
        "Front": "親友",
        "Back": "close friend,buddy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 787
    },
    {
        "Front": "信用",
        "Back": "confidence,dependence,credit,faith",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 788
    },
    {
        "Front": "信頼",
        "Back": "reliance,trust,confidence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 789
    },
    {
        "Front": "心理",
        "Back": "mentality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 790
    },
    {
        "Front": "人類",
        "Back": "mankind,humanity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 791
    },
    {
        "Front": "巣",
        "Back": "nest,rookery,breeding place,beehive,cobweb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 792
    },
    {
        "Front": "図",
        "Back": "figure (e.g. Fig 1),drawing,picture,illustration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 793
    },
    {
        "Front": "水準",
        "Back": "(1) water level,(2) level,standard",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 794
    },
    {
        "Front": "推薦",
        "Back": "recommendation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 795
    },
    {
        "Front": "スイッチ",
        "Back": "switch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "随分",
        "Back": "extremely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 796
    },
    {
        "Front": "睡眠",
        "Back": "sleep",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 797
    },
    {
        "Front": "数字",
        "Back": "numeral,figure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 798
    },
    {
        "Front": "スープ",
        "Back": "(Western) soup",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "末",
        "Back": "the end of,powder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 799
    },
    {
        "Front": "姿",
        "Back": "figure,shape,appearance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 800
    },
    {
        "Front": "スキー",
        "Back": "skiing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "空く",
        "Back": "(1) to open,to become empty,(2) to be less crowded",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 801
    },
    {
        "Front": "救う",
        "Back": "to rescue from,to help out of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 802
    },
    {
        "Front": "優れる",
        "Back": "to surpass,to outstrip,to excel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 803
    },
    {
        "Front": "スケート",
        "Back": "skate(s),skating",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "すごい",
        "Back": "terrible,dreadful,terrific,amazing,great",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "少しも",
        "Back": "anything of,not one bit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 804
    },
    {
        "Front": "過ごす",
        "Back": "to pass,to spend,to go through,to tide over",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 805
    },
    {
        "Front": "筋",
        "Back": "muscle,string,line",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 806
    },
    {
        "Front": "進める",
        "Back": "to advance,to promote,to hasten",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 807
    },
    {
        "Front": "勧める",
        "Back": "to recommend,to advise,to encourage,to offer (wine)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 808
    },
    {
        "Front": "スター",
        "Back": "star",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "スタイル",
        "Back": "style",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "スタンド",
        "Back": "stand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "頭痛",
        "Back": "headache",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 809
    },
    {
        "Front": "ずっと",
        "Back": "consecutively,throughout,a lot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "すてき",
        "Back": "lovely,dreamy,beautiful,great",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "既に",
        "Back": "already,too late",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 810
    },
    {
        "Front": "すなわち",
        "Back": "that is,namely,i.e.",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "素晴らしい",
        "Back": "wonderful,splendid,magnificent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 811
    },
    {
        "Front": "スピーチ",
        "Back": "speech",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "全て",
        "Back": "all,the whole,entirely,in general,wholly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 812
    },
    {
        "Front": "済ませる",
        "Back": "to be finished",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 813
    },
    {
        "Front": "角",
        "Back": "horn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 814
    },
    {
        "Front": "すみません",
        "Back": "sorry,excuse me",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "為る",
        "Back": "to change,to be of use,to reach to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 816
    },
    {
        "Front": "すると",
        "Back": "thereupon,hereupon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "鋭い",
        "Back": "pointed,sharp",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 818
    },
    {
        "Front": "背",
        "Back": "height,stature",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 819
    },
    {
        "Front": "正",
        "Back": "(logical) true,regular",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 820
    },
    {
        "Front": "生",
        "Back": "(1) draft (beer),(2) raw,unprocessed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 821
    },
    {
        "Front": "性",
        "Back": "sex,gender",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 822
    },
    {
        "Front": "所為",
        "Back": "cause,reason,fault",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 823
    },
    {
        "Front": "税",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 824
    },
    {
        "Front": "性格",
        "Back": "character,personality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 825
    },
    {
        "Front": "正確",
        "Back": "accurate,punctuality,exactness,authenticity,veracity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 826
    },
    {
        "Front": "世紀",
        "Back": "century,era",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 827
    },
    {
        "Front": "請求",
        "Back": "claim,demand,application,request",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 828
    },
    {
        "Front": "税金",
        "Back": "tax,duty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 829
    },
    {
        "Front": "清潔",
        "Back": "clean",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 830
    },
    {
        "Front": "制限",
        "Back": "restriction,restraint,limitation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 831
    },
    {
        "Front": "成功",
        "Back": "success,hit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 832
    },
    {
        "Front": "生産",
        "Back": "production,manufacture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 833
    },
    {
        "Front": "正式",
        "Back": "due form,official,formality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 834
    },
    {
        "Front": "精神",
        "Back": "mind,soul,heart,spirit,intention",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 835
    },
    {
        "Front": "成人",
        "Back": "adult",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 836
    },
    {
        "Front": "精々",
        "Back": "at the most,at best,to the utmost,as much (far) as possible",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 837
    },
    {
        "Front": "成績",
        "Back": "results,record",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 838
    },
    {
        "Front": "製造",
        "Back": "manufacture,production",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 839
    },
    {
        "Front": "贅沢",
        "Back": "luxury,extravagance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 840
    },
    {
        "Front": "成長",
        "Back": "growth,grow to adulthood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 841
    },
    {
        "Front": "制度",
        "Back": "system,institution,organization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 842
    },
    {
        "Front": "青年",
        "Back": "youth,young man",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 843
    },
    {
        "Front": "製品",
        "Back": "manufactured goods,finished goods",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 844
    },
    {
        "Front": "政府",
        "Back": "government,administration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 845
    },
    {
        "Front": "生物",
        "Back": "raw food",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 846
    },
    {
        "Front": "生命",
        "Back": "life,existence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 847
    },
    {
        "Front": "整理",
        "Back": "sorting,arrangement,adjustment,regulation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 848
    },
    {
        "Front": "咳",
        "Back": "cough",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 849
    },
    {
        "Front": "石炭",
        "Back": "coal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 850
    },
    {
        "Front": "責任",
        "Back": "duty,responsibility",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 851
    },
    {
        "Front": "石油",
        "Back": "oil,petroleum,kerosene",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 852
    },
    {
        "Front": "世間",
        "Back": "world,society",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 853
    },
    {
        "Front": "説",
        "Back": "theory",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 854
    },
    {
        "Front": "積極的",
        "Back": "positive,active,proactive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 855
    },
    {
        "Front": "設計",
        "Back": "plan,design",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 856
    },
    {
        "Front": "絶対",
        "Back": "absolute,unconditional,absoluteness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 857
    },
    {
        "Front": "セット",
        "Back": "set",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "設備",
        "Back": "equipment,device,facilities,installation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 858
    },
    {
        "Front": "絶滅",
        "Back": "destruction,extinction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 859
    },
    {
        "Front": "節約",
        "Back": "economising,saving",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 860
    },
    {
        "Front": "是非",
        "Back": "certainly,without fail",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 861
    },
    {
        "Front": "責める",
        "Back": "to condemn,to blame,to criticize",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 862
    },
    {
        "Front": "世話",
        "Back": "looking after,help,aid,assistance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 863
    },
    {
        "Front": "善",
        "Back": "good,goodness,right,virtue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 864
    },
    {
        "Front": "全",
        "Back": "all,whole,entire,complete,overall,pan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 865
    },
    {
        "Front": "全員",
        "Back": "all members (unanimity),all hands,the whole crew",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 866
    },
    {
        "Front": "専攻",
        "Back": "major subject,special study",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 867
    },
    {
        "Front": "全国",
        "Back": "country-wide,nation-wide,whole country,national",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 868
    },
    {
        "Front": "先日",
        "Back": "the other day,a few days ago",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 869
    },
    {
        "Front": "前者",
        "Back": "the former",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 870
    },
    {
        "Front": "選手",
        "Back": "(1) player (in game),(2) team",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 871
    },
    {
        "Front": "前進",
        "Back": "advance,drive,progress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 872
    },
    {
        "Front": "全然",
        "Back": "(1) wholly,entirely,completely,(2) not at all (with neg. verb)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 873
    },
    {
        "Front": "センター",
        "Back": "a center",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "全体",
        "Back": "whole,entirety,whatever (is the matter)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 874
    },
    {
        "Front": "選択",
        "Back": "selection,choice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 875
    },
    {
        "Front": "そう",
        "Back": "so",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "象",
        "Back": "elephant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 877
    },
    {
        "Front": "騒音",
        "Back": "noise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 878
    },
    {
        "Front": "増加",
        "Back": "increase,addition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 879
    },
    {
        "Front": "操作",
        "Back": "operation,management,processing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 880
    },
    {
        "Front": "掃除",
        "Back": "cleaning,sweeping",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 881
    },
    {
        "Front": "想像",
        "Back": "imagination,guess",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 882
    },
    {
        "Front": "相続",
        "Back": "succession,inheritance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 883
    },
    {
        "Front": "相談",
        "Back": "consultation,discussion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 884
    },
    {
        "Front": "装置",
        "Back": "equipment,installation,apparatus",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 885
    },
    {
        "Front": "相当",
        "Back": "suitable,fair,tolerable,proper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 886
    },
    {
        "Front": "速度",
        "Back": "speed,velocity,rate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 887
    },
    {
        "Front": "そこ",
        "Back": "bottom,sole",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "底",
        "Back": "bottom,sole",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 889
    },
    {
        "Front": "そこで",
        "Back": "so (conj),accordingly,now,then,thereupon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "組織",
        "Back": "(1) organization,(2) structure,construction,(3) tissue,(4) system",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 890
    },
    {
        "Front": "そして",
        "Back": "and",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "注ぐ",
        "Back": "to pour (into),to irrigate,to pay,to fill,to feed (e.g. a fire)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 891
    },
    {
        "Front": "育つ",
        "Back": "to raise (child),to be brought up,to grow (up)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 892
    },
    {
        "Front": "そっくり",
        "Back": "all,altogether,entirely,be just like,the splitting image of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "そっと",
        "Back": "face of the earth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "袖",
        "Back": "sleeve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 893
    },
    {
        "Front": "備える",
        "Back": "to furnish,to provide for,to equip,to install",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 894
    },
    {
        "Front": "その",
        "Back": "the,that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "そのうち",
        "Back": "eventually,sooner or later,of the previously mentioned",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "そのまま",
        "Back": "without change,as it is (i.e. now)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "側",
        "Back": "side,edge,third person",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 896
    },
    {
        "Front": "ソファー",
        "Back": "sofa,couch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "粗末",
        "Back": "crude,rough,plain,humble",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 897
    },
    {
        "Front": "それ",
        "Back": "it,that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "それぞれ",
        "Back": "each,every,either,respectively,severally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "それでも",
        "Back": "but (still),and yet,nevertheless,even so,notwithstanding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "それと",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "それとも",
        "Back": "or,or else",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "損",
        "Back": "loss,disadvantage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 899
    },
    {
        "Front": "損害",
        "Back": "damage,injury,loss",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 900
    },
    {
        "Front": "尊敬",
        "Back": "respect,esteem,reverence,honour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 901
    },
    {
        "Front": "存在",
        "Back": "existence,being",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 902
    },
    {
        "Front": "尊重",
        "Back": "respect,esteem,regard",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 903
    },
    {
        "Front": "田",
        "Back": "rice field",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 904
    },
    {
        "Front": "他",
        "Back": "other (esp. places and things)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 905
    },
    {
        "Front": "対",
        "Back": "pair,couple,set",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 906
    },
    {
        "Front": "大",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 907
    },
    {
        "Front": "台",
        "Back": "stand,rack,table,support",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 908
    },
    {
        "Front": "題",
        "Back": "title,subject,theme,topic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 909
    },
    {
        "Front": "体育",
        "Back": "physical education,gymnastics,athletics",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 910
    },
    {
        "Front": "体温",
        "Back": "temperature (body)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 911
    },
    {
        "Front": "大会",
        "Back": "convention,tournament,mass meeting,rally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 912
    },
    {
        "Front": "大気",
        "Back": "atmosphere",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 913
    },
    {
        "Front": "代金",
        "Back": "price,payment,cost,charge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 914
    },
    {
        "Front": "退屈",
        "Back": "tedium,boredom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 915
    },
    {
        "Front": "滞在",
        "Back": "stay,sojourn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 916
    },
    {
        "Front": "大使",
        "Back": "ambassador",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 917
    },
    {
        "Front": "大した",
        "Back": "considerable,great,important,significant,a big deal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 918
    },
    {
        "Front": "対象",
        "Back": "target,object (of worship, study, etc),subject (of taxation, etc)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 919
    },
    {
        "Front": "大臣",
        "Back": "cabinet minister",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 920
    },
    {
        "Front": "対する",
        "Back": "to face,to confront,to oppose",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 921
    },
    {
        "Front": "大戦",
        "Back": "great war,great battle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 922
    },
    {
        "Front": "大抵",
        "Back": "usually,generally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 923
    },
    {
        "Front": "態度",
        "Back": "attitude,manner",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 924
    },
    {
        "Front": "大統領",
        "Back": "president,chief executive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 925
    },
    {
        "Front": "大半",
        "Back": "majority,mostly,generally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 926
    },
    {
        "Front": "代表",
        "Back": "representative,representation,delegation,type,example,model",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 927
    },
    {
        "Front": "大部分",
        "Back": "most part,greater part,majority",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 928
    },
    {
        "Front": "タイプライター",
        "Back": "typewriter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "大変",
        "Back": "awful,dreadful,terrible,very",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 929
    },
    {
        "Front": "逮捕",
        "Back": "arrest,apprehension,capture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 930
    },
    {
        "Front": "ダイヤ",
        "Back": "(1) dyer,(2) diagram,(3) (railway) schedule,(4) diamond",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "太陽",
        "Back": "sun,solar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 931
    },
    {
        "Front": "平ら",
        "Back": "flatness,level,smooth,calm,plain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 932
    },
    {
        "Front": "代理",
        "Back": "representation,agency,proxy,deputy,agent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 933
    },
    {
        "Front": "大陸",
        "Back": "continent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 934
    },
    {
        "Front": "倒す",
        "Back": "to throw down,to beat,to bring down,to blow down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 935
    },
    {
        "Front": "タオル",
        "Back": "(hand) towel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "だが",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "互い",
        "Back": "mutual,reciprocal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 937
    },
    {
        "Front": "宝",
        "Back": "treasure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 938
    },
    {
        "Front": "だから",
        "Back": "so,therefore",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "宅",
        "Back": "house,home,husband",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 940
    },
    {
        "Front": "だけど",
        "Back": "however",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "確かめる",
        "Back": "to ascertain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 941
    },
    {
        "Front": "多少",
        "Back": "more or less,somewhat,a little,some",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 942
    },
    {
        "Front": "助ける",
        "Back": "to help,to save,to rescue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 943
    },
    {
        "Front": "ただ",
        "Back": "free of charge,mere,only",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "唯",
        "Back": "free of charge,mere,sole,only,usual,common",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 944
    },
    {
        "Front": "戦い",
        "Back": "battle,fight,struggle,conflict",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 945
    },
    {
        "Front": "戦う",
        "Back": "to fight,to battle,to combat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 946
    },
    {
        "Front": "叩く",
        "Back": "to strike,to clap,to dust,to beat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 947
    },
    {
        "Front": "直ちに",
        "Back": "at once,immediately,directly,in person",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 948
    },
    {
        "Front": "立ち上がる",
        "Back": "to stand up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 949
    },
    {
        "Front": "立場",
        "Back": "standpoint,position,situation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 950
    },
    {
        "Front": "経つ",
        "Back": "to pass,to lapse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 951
    },
    {
        "Front": "達する",
        "Back": "to reach,to get to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 952
    },
    {
        "Front": "だって",
        "Back": "but,because,even,also,too",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "たっぷり",
        "Back": "full,in plenty,ample",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "縦",
        "Back": "length,height",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 953
    },
    {
        "Front": "たとえ",
        "Back": "simile,metaphor,allegory",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "谷",
        "Back": "valley",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 954
    },
    {
        "Front": "他人",
        "Back": "another person,unrelated person,outsider,stranger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 955
    },
    {
        "Front": "種",
        "Back": "(1) seed,(2) material,(3) cause,source",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 956
    },
    {
        "Front": "束",
        "Back": "handbreadth,bundle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 957
    },
    {
        "Front": "度",
        "Back": "counter for occurrences",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 958
    },
    {
        "Front": "旅",
        "Back": "travel,trip,journey",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 959
    },
    {
        "Front": "たびたび",
        "Back": "often,repeatedly,frequently",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "多分",
        "Back": "perhaps,probably",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 960
    },
    {
        "Front": "玉",
        "Back": "ball,sphere,coin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 961
    },
    {
        "Front": "弾",
        "Back": "bullet,shot,shell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 962
    },
    {
        "Front": "偶",
        "Back": "even number,couple,man and wife,friend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 963
    },
    {
        "Front": "偶々",
        "Back": "casually,unexpectedly,accidentally,by chance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 964
    },
    {
        "Front": "たまらない",
        "Back": "intolerable,unbearable,unendurable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "黙る",
        "Back": "to be silent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 965
    },
    {
        "Front": "駄目",
        "Back": "useless,no good,hopeless",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 966
    },
    {
        "Front": "試し",
        "Back": "trial,test",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 967
    },
    {
        "Front": "試す",
        "Back": "to attempt,to test",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 968
    },
    {
        "Front": "便り",
        "Back": "news,tidings,information,correspondence,letter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 969
    },
    {
        "Front": "頼る",
        "Back": "to rely on,to have recourse to,to depend on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 970
    },
    {
        "Front": "段",
        "Back": "step,stair,flight of steps,grade,rank,level",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 972
    },
    {
        "Front": "誰か",
        "Back": "someone,somebody",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 971
    },
    {
        "Front": "単位",
        "Back": "unit,denomination,credit (in school)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 973
    },
    {
        "Front": "単語",
        "Back": "word,vocabulary,(usually) single-character word",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 974
    },
    {
        "Front": "男子",
        "Back": "youth,young man",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 975
    },
    {
        "Front": "単純",
        "Back": "simplicity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 976
    },
    {
        "Front": "誕生",
        "Back": "birth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 977
    },
    {
        "Front": "ダンス",
        "Back": "dance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "団体",
        "Back": "organization,association",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 978
    },
    {
        "Front": "担当",
        "Back": "(in) charge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 979
    },
    {
        "Front": "単なる",
        "Back": "mere,simple,sheer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 980
    },
    {
        "Front": "単に",
        "Back": "simply,merely,only,solely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 981
    },
    {
        "Front": "地",
        "Back": "earth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 982
    },
    {
        "Front": "地位",
        "Back": "(social) position,status",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 983
    },
    {
        "Front": "地域",
        "Back": "area,region",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 984
    },
    {
        "Front": "チーズ",
        "Back": "cheese",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "チーム",
        "Back": "team",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "知恵",
        "Back": "wisdom,wit,sagacity,sense,intelligence,advice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 985
    },
    {
        "Front": "地下",
        "Back": "basement,underground",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 986
    },
    {
        "Front": "違い",
        "Back": "difference,discrepancy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 987
    },
    {
        "Front": "違いない",
        "Back": "(phrase) sure,no mistaking it,for certain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 988
    },
    {
        "Front": "近頃",
        "Back": "lately,recently,nowadays",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 989
    },
    {
        "Front": "地球",
        "Back": "the earth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 990
    },
    {
        "Front": "地区",
        "Back": "district,section,sector",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 991
    },
    {
        "Front": "遅刻",
        "Back": "lateness,late coming",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 992
    },
    {
        "Front": "知事",
        "Back": "prefectural governor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 993
    },
    {
        "Front": "知識",
        "Back": "knowledge,information",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 994
    },
    {
        "Front": "父親",
        "Back": "father",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 995
    },
    {
        "Front": "知能",
        "Back": "intelligence,brains",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 996
    },
    {
        "Front": "地平線",
        "Back": "horizon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 997
    },
    {
        "Front": "地方",
        "Back": "area,locality,district,region,the coast",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 998
    },
    {
        "Front": "茶",
        "Back": "tea",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 999
    },
    {
        "Front": "チャンス",
        "Back": "chance,opportunity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ちゃんと",
        "Back": "perfectly,properly,exactly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "中",
        "Back": "inside,middle,among",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1000
    },
    {
        "Front": "注",
        "Back": "annotation,explanatory note",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1001
    },
    {
        "Front": "中央",
        "Back": "centre,central,center,middle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1002
    },
    {
        "Front": "中学",
        "Back": "middle school,junior high school",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1003
    },
    {
        "Front": "中古",
        "Back": "(1) used,second-hand,old",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1004
    },
    {
        "Front": "中止",
        "Back": "suspension,stoppage,discontinuance,interruption",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1005
    },
    {
        "Front": "駐車",
        "Back": "parking (e.g. car)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1006
    },
    {
        "Front": "昼食",
        "Back": "lunch,midday meal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1007
    },
    {
        "Front": "中心",
        "Back": "center,core,heart,pivot,emphasis,balance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1008
    },
    {
        "Front": "注目",
        "Back": "notice,attention,observation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1009
    },
    {
        "Front": "注文",
        "Back": "order,request",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1010
    },
    {
        "Front": "長期",
        "Back": "long time period",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1011
    },
    {
        "Front": "調査",
        "Back": "investigation,examination,inquiry,survey",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1012
    },
    {
        "Front": "調子",
        "Back": "tune,tone,key",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1013
    },
    {
        "Front": "頂上",
        "Back": "top,summit,peak",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1014
    },
    {
        "Front": "ちょうだい",
        "Back": "(1) please do for me (preceded by -te),(2) reception,being given,get",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "貯金",
        "Back": "(bank) savings",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1015
    },
    {
        "Front": "直接",
        "Back": "direct,immediate,personal,firsthand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1016
    },
    {
        "Front": "著者",
        "Back": "author,writer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1017
    },
    {
        "Front": "遂に",
        "Back": "finally,at last",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1018
    },
    {
        "Front": "通過",
        "Back": "passage through,passing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1019
    },
    {
        "Front": "通学",
        "Back": "commuting to school",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1020
    },
    {
        "Front": "通行",
        "Back": "passage,passing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1021
    },
    {
        "Front": "通じる",
        "Back": "to run to,to lead to,to communicate,to understand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1022
    },
    {
        "Front": "通信",
        "Back": "correspondence,communication,news,signal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1023
    },
    {
        "Front": "捕まる",
        "Back": "to be caught,to be arrested",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1024
    },
    {
        "Front": "掴む",
        "Back": "to seize,to catch,to grasp",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1025
    },
    {
        "Front": "疲れ",
        "Back": "tiredness,fatigue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1026
    },
    {
        "Front": "月",
        "Back": "moon,month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1027
    },
    {
        "Front": "付き合い",
        "Back": "association,socializing,fellowship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1028
    },
    {
        "Front": "次々",
        "Back": "in succession,one by one",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1029
    },
    {
        "Front": "就く",
        "Back": "to settle in (place),to take (seat, position),to study (under teacher)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1030
    },
    {
        "Front": "付ける",
        "Back": "to attach,to join,to add,to append",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1031
    },
    {
        "Front": "土",
        "Back": "earth,soil",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1032
    },
    {
        "Front": "続き",
        "Back": "sequel,continuation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1033
    },
    {
        "Front": "包み",
        "Back": "bundle,package,parcel,bale",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1034
    },
    {
        "Front": "勤め",
        "Back": "(1) service,duty,business,responsibility,task,(2) Buddhist religious services",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1035
    },
    {
        "Front": "務め",
        "Back": "(1) service,duty,(2) Buddhist religious services",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1036
    },
    {
        "Front": "繋ぐ",
        "Back": "to tie,to fasten,to connect,to transfer (phone call)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1037
    },
    {
        "Front": "常に",
        "Back": "always,constantly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1038
    },
    {
        "Front": "翼",
        "Back": "wings",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1039
    },
    {
        "Front": "つまり",
        "Back": "in short,in brief,in other words",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "罪",
        "Back": "crime,fault,indiscretion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1040
    },
    {
        "Front": "詰める",
        "Back": "to pack,to shorten,to work out (details)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1041
    },
    {
        "Front": "積もる",
        "Back": "to pile up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1042
    },
    {
        "Front": "梅雨",
        "Back": "rainy season,rain during the rainy season",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1043
    },
    {
        "Front": "辛い",
        "Back": "painful,heart-breaking",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1044
    },
    {
        "Front": "釣",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1045
    },
    {
        "Front": "連れ",
        "Back": "companion,company",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1046
    },
    {
        "Front": "で",
        "Back": "outflow,coming (going) out,graduate (of)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "出会い",
        "Back": "meeting,rendezvous,encounter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1047
    },
    {
        "Front": "出会う",
        "Back": "to meet by chance,to come across,to happen to encounter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1048
    },
    {
        "Front": "提案",
        "Back": "proposal,proposition,suggestion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1049
    },
    {
        "Front": "定期",
        "Back": "fixed term",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1050
    },
    {
        "Front": "抵抗",
        "Back": "electrical resistance,resistance,opposition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1051
    },
    {
        "Front": "提出",
        "Back": "presentation,submission,filing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1052
    },
    {
        "Front": "程度",
        "Back": "degree,amount,grade,standard,of the order of (following a number)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1053
    },
    {
        "Front": "停留所",
        "Back": "bus or tram stop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1054
    },
    {
        "Front": "デート",
        "Back": "date,go on a date",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "敵",
        "Back": "enemy,rival",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1055
    },
    {
        "Front": "出来事",
        "Back": "incident,affair,happening,event",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1056
    },
    {
        "Front": "適する",
        "Back": "to fit,to suit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1057
    },
    {
        "Front": "適切",
        "Back": "pertinent,appropriate,adequate,relevance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1058
    },
    {
        "Front": "適度",
        "Back": "moderate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1059
    },
    {
        "Front": "適用",
        "Back": "applying",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1060
    },
    {
        "Front": "できる",
        "Back": "to be able to,to be ready,to occur",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "出来るだけ",
        "Back": "if at all possible",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1062
    },
    {
        "Front": "できれば",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "手品",
        "Back": "sleight of hand,conjuring trick,magic,juggling",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1063
    },
    {
        "Front": "ですから",
        "Back": "therefore",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "鉄",
        "Back": "iron",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1064
    },
    {
        "Front": "哲学",
        "Back": "philosophy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1065
    },
    {
        "Front": "手伝い",
        "Back": "help,helper,assistant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1066
    },
    {
        "Front": "徹底",
        "Back": "thoroughness,completeness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1067
    },
    {
        "Front": "鉄道",
        "Back": "railroad",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1068
    },
    {
        "Front": "徹夜",
        "Back": "all night,all night vigil,sleepless night",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1069
    },
    {
        "Front": "では",
        "Back": "chance of going out,opportunity (to succeed),moment of departure,beginning of work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "手間",
        "Back": "time,labour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1071
    },
    {
        "Front": "でも",
        "Back": "but,however",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "デモ",
        "Back": "(abbr) demo,demonstration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "典型",
        "Back": "type,pattern,archetypal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1073
    },
    {
        "Front": "天候",
        "Back": "weather",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1074
    },
    {
        "Front": "電子",
        "Back": "electron",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1075
    },
    {
        "Front": "テント",
        "Back": "tent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "伝統",
        "Back": "tradition,convention",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1076
    },
    {
        "Front": "天然",
        "Back": "nature,spontaneity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1077
    },
    {
        "Front": "問い",
        "Back": "question,query",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1078
    },
    {
        "Front": "党",
        "Back": "party (political)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1079
    },
    {
        "Front": "塔",
        "Back": "tower,pagoda",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1080
    },
    {
        "Front": "どう",
        "Back": "child,servant,foolishness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "答案",
        "Back": "examination paper,examination script",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1081
    },
    {
        "Front": "同一",
        "Back": "identity,sameness,similarity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1083
    },
    {
        "Front": "どうか",
        "Back": "copper coin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "当時",
        "Back": "at that time,in those days",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1084
    },
    {
        "Front": "動詞",
        "Back": "verb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1085
    },
    {
        "Front": "同時",
        "Back": "simultaneous(ly),concurrent,same time,synchronous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1086
    },
    {
        "Front": "どうしても",
        "Back": "by all means,at any cost,no matter what",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "到着",
        "Back": "arrival",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1087
    },
    {
        "Front": "道徳",
        "Back": "morals",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1088
    },
    {
        "Front": "投票",
        "Back": "voting,poll",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1089
    },
    {
        "Front": "同様",
        "Back": "identical,equal to,same (kind),like",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1090
    },
    {
        "Front": "同僚",
        "Back": "coworker,colleague,associate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1091
    },
    {
        "Front": "道路",
        "Back": "road,highway",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1093
    },
    {
        "Front": "通す",
        "Back": "to let pass,to overlook,to continue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1092
    },
    {
        "Front": "通り",
        "Back": "in accordance with ~,following ~,~ Street,~ Avenue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1094
    },
    {
        "Front": "通り過ぎる",
        "Back": "to pass,to pass through",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1095
    },
    {
        "Front": "都会",
        "Back": "city",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1096
    },
    {
        "Front": "時",
        "Back": "(1) time,hour,(2) occasion,moment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1097
    },
    {
        "Front": "解く",
        "Back": "to unfasten",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1098
    },
    {
        "Front": "毒",
        "Back": "poison,toxicant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1099
    },
    {
        "Front": "得意",
        "Back": "pride,triumph,prosperity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1100
    },
    {
        "Front": "読書",
        "Back": "reading",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1101
    },
    {
        "Front": "独身",
        "Back": "bachelorhood,single,unmarried,celibate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1102
    },
    {
        "Front": "特徴",
        "Back": "feature,characteristic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1103
    },
    {
        "Front": "独特",
        "Back": "peculiarity,uniqueness,characteristic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1104
    },
    {
        "Front": "独立",
        "Back": "independence (e.g. Ind. Day),self-support",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1105
    },
    {
        "Front": "解ける",
        "Back": "to come untied,to come apart",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1106
    },
    {
        "Front": "どこか",
        "Back": "somewhere,anywhere",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ところが",
        "Back": "however,while,even if",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ところで",
        "Back": "by the way,even if,no matter what",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "登山",
        "Back": "mountain-climbing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1107
    },
    {
        "Front": "都市",
        "Back": "town,city,municipal,urban",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1108
    },
    {
        "Front": "年月",
        "Back": "months and years",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1109
    },
    {
        "Front": "図書",
        "Back": "books",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1110
    },
    {
        "Front": "年寄",
        "Back": "old people,the aged",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1111
    },
    {
        "Front": "閉じる",
        "Back": "to close (e.g. book, eyes),to shut",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1112
    },
    {
        "Front": "途端",
        "Back": "just (now, at the moment, etc.)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1113
    },
    {
        "Front": "土地",
        "Back": "plot of land,lot,soil",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1114
    },
    {
        "Front": "突然",
        "Back": "abruptly,suddenly,unexpectedly,all at once",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1115
    },
    {
        "Front": "トップ",
        "Back": "top",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "届く",
        "Back": "to reach",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1116
    },
    {
        "Front": "とにかく",
        "Back": "anyhow,at any rate,anyway,somehow or other,generally speaking,in any case",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "飛ばす",
        "Back": "to skip over,to omit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1117
    },
    {
        "Front": "飛び出す",
        "Back": "to jump out,to rush out,to fly out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1118
    },
    {
        "Front": "留める",
        "Back": "to fasten,to turn off,to detain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1119
    },
    {
        "Front": "友",
        "Back": "friend,companion,pal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1120
    },
    {
        "Front": "共に",
        "Back": "sharing with,participate in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1121
    },
    {
        "Front": "土曜",
        "Back": "Saturday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1122
    },
    {
        "Front": "虎",
        "Back": "tiger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1123
    },
    {
        "Front": "ドライブ",
        "Back": "drive,trip by car,driving",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "トラック",
        "Back": "(1) truck,(2) (running) track",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ドラマ",
        "Back": "drama",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "トランプ",
        "Back": "playing cards (lit: trump)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り上げる",
        "Back": "to take up,to pick up,to disqualify,to confiscate,to deprive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1124
    },
    {
        "Front": "努力",
        "Back": "great effort,exertion,endeavour,effort",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1125
    },
    {
        "Front": "どれ",
        "Back": "well,now,let me see,which (of three or more)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ドレス",
        "Back": "dress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "取れる",
        "Back": "to come off,to be taken off,to be removed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1127
    },
    {
        "Front": "泥",
        "Back": "mud",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1128
    },
    {
        "Front": "とん",
        "Back": "ton",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "とんでもない",
        "Back": "unexpected,offensive,What a thing to say!,No way!",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "どんな",
        "Back": "what,what kind of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "どんなに",
        "Back": "how,how much",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "トンネル",
        "Back": "tunnel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "名",
        "Back": "name,reputation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1130
    },
    {
        "Front": "内容",
        "Back": "subject,contents,matter,substance,detail,import",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1131
    },
    {
        "Front": "なお",
        "Back": "straight,mischief,ordinary,common",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "仲",
        "Back": "relation,relationship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1132
    },
    {
        "Front": "流す",
        "Back": "to drain,to float,to shed (blood, tears),to cruise (e.g. taxi)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1133
    },
    {
        "Front": "なかなか",
        "Back": "very,considerably,easily",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "半ば",
        "Back": "middle,half,semi,halfway,partly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1134
    },
    {
        "Front": "仲間",
        "Back": "company,fellow,colleague,associate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1135
    },
    {
        "Front": "眺め",
        "Back": "scene,view,prospect,outlook",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1136
    },
    {
        "Front": "眺める",
        "Back": "to view,to gaze at",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1137
    },
    {
        "Front": "流れ",
        "Back": "stream,current",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1138
    },
    {
        "Front": "流れる",
        "Back": "to stream,to flow,to run (ink),to be washed away",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1139
    },
    {
        "Front": "無し",
        "Back": "without",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1140
    },
    {
        "Front": "なぜなら",
        "Back": "because",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "謎",
        "Back": "riddle,puzzle,enigma",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1141
    },
    {
        "Front": "納得",
        "Back": "consent,assent,understanding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1142
    },
    {
        "Front": "等",
        "Back": "et cetera,etc.,and the like",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1143
    },
    {
        "Front": "何",
        "Back": "what",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1144
    },
    {
        "Front": "何か",
        "Back": "something",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1145
    },
    {
        "Front": "なにも",
        "Back": "nothing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "鍋",
        "Back": "saucepan,pot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1146
    },
    {
        "Front": "怠ける",
        "Back": "to be idle,to neglect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1147
    },
    {
        "Front": "波",
        "Back": "wave",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1148
    },
    {
        "Front": "涙",
        "Back": "tear",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1149
    },
    {
        "Front": "悩む",
        "Back": "to be worried,to be troubled",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1150
    },
    {
        "Front": "成る",
        "Back": "to become",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1151
    },
    {
        "Front": "縄",
        "Back": "rope,hemp",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1152
    },
    {
        "Front": "何で",
        "Back": "Why?,What for?",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1153
    },
    {
        "Front": "何でも",
        "Back": "by all means,everything",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1154
    },
    {
        "Front": "何とか",
        "Back": "somehow,anyhow,one way or another",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1155
    },
    {
        "Front": "似合う",
        "Back": "to suit,to match,to become,to be like",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1156
    },
    {
        "Front": "匂い",
        "Back": "odour,scent,smell,stench",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1157
    },
    {
        "Front": "苦手",
        "Back": "poor (at),weak (in),dislike (of)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1158
    },
    {
        "Front": "握る",
        "Back": "to grasp,to seize,to mould sushi",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1159
    },
    {
        "Front": "日",
        "Back": "sun,sunshine,day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1160
    },
    {
        "Front": "日常",
        "Back": "ordinary,regular,everyday,usual",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1161
    },
    {
        "Front": "日曜",
        "Back": "Sunday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1162
    },
    {
        "Front": "日光",
        "Back": "sunlight",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1163
    },
    {
        "Front": "日中",
        "Back": "daytime,broad daylight",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1164
    },
    {
        "Front": "にっこり",
        "Back": "smile sweetly,smile,grin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "日本",
        "Back": "Japan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1165
    },
    {
        "Front": "入院",
        "Back": "hospitalization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1166
    },
    {
        "Front": "入学",
        "Back": "entry to school or university,matriculation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1167
    },
    {
        "Front": "入場",
        "Back": "entrance,admission,entering",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1168
    },
    {
        "Front": "人気",
        "Back": "sign of life",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1169
    },
    {
        "Front": "人間",
        "Back": "human being,man,person",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1170
    },
    {
        "Front": "抜く",
        "Back": "to extract,to omit,to surpass,to draw out,to unplug",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1171
    },
    {
        "Front": "抜ける",
        "Back": "to come out,to fall out,to be omitted",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1172
    },
    {
        "Front": "布",
        "Back": "cloth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1173
    },
    {
        "Front": "濡れる",
        "Back": "to get wet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1174
    },
    {
        "Front": "ね",
        "Back": "value,price,cost,worth,merit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "根",
        "Back": "root",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1176
    },
    {
        "Front": "値",
        "Back": "value,price,cost",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1177
    },
    {
        "Front": "願い",
        "Back": "desire,wish,request",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1178
    },
    {
        "Front": "願う",
        "Back": "to desire,to wish,to request",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1179
    },
    {
        "Front": "鼠",
        "Back": "(1) mouse,rat,(2) dark gray,slate color",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1180
    },
    {
        "Front": "値段",
        "Back": "price,cost",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1181
    },
    {
        "Front": "熱心",
        "Back": "zeal,enthusiasm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1182
    },
    {
        "Front": "熱帯",
        "Back": "tropics",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1183
    },
    {
        "Front": "熱中",
        "Back": "nuts!,enthusiasm,zeal,mania",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1184
    },
    {
        "Front": "年間",
        "Back": "year",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1185
    },
    {
        "Front": "年中",
        "Back": "whole year,always,everyday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1186
    },
    {
        "Front": "年代",
        "Back": "age,era,period,date",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1187
    },
    {
        "Front": "年齢",
        "Back": "age,years",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1188
    },
    {
        "Front": "野",
        "Back": "field",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1189
    },
    {
        "Front": "能",
        "Back": "being skilled in,nicely,properly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1190
    },
    {
        "Front": "農家",
        "Back": "farmer,farm family",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1191
    },
    {
        "Front": "農業",
        "Back": "agriculture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1192
    },
    {
        "Front": "農民",
        "Back": "farmers,peasants",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1193
    },
    {
        "Front": "能力",
        "Back": "ability,faculty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1194
    },
    {
        "Front": "ノー",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "残す",
        "Back": "to leave (behind, over),to bequeath,to save,to reserve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1196
    },
    {
        "Front": "残り",
        "Back": "remnant,residue,remaining,left-over",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1197
    },
    {
        "Front": "乗せる",
        "Back": "to place on (something),to take on board,to give a ride",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1198
    },
    {
        "Front": "除く",
        "Back": "to remove,to exclude,to except",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1199
    },
    {
        "Front": "望み",
        "Back": "wish,desire,(a) hope",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1200
    },
    {
        "Front": "望む",
        "Back": "to desire,to wish for,to see,to command (a view of)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1201
    },
    {
        "Front": "ノック",
        "Back": "(1) knock,(2) fungo (baseball)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "喉",
        "Back": "throat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1202
    },
    {
        "Front": "伸ばす",
        "Back": "to lengthen,to stretch,to reach out,to grow (beard)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1203
    },
    {
        "Front": "伸びる",
        "Back": "to stretch,to extend,to make progress,to grow (beard, body height)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1204
    },
    {
        "Front": "述べる",
        "Back": "to state,to express,to mention",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1205
    },
    {
        "Front": "昇る",
        "Back": "to arise,to ascend,to go up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1206
    },
    {
        "Front": "のんびり",
        "Back": "carefree,at leisure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "場",
        "Back": "place,field (physics)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1207
    },
    {
        "Front": "はあ",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "パーセント",
        "Back": "percent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "はい",
        "Back": "wear,put on (sword)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "灰",
        "Back": "ash",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1210
    },
    {
        "Front": "バイオリン",
        "Back": "violin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ハイキング",
        "Back": "hiking",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "配達",
        "Back": "delivery,distribution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1211
    },
    {
        "Front": "パイプ",
        "Back": "(1) pipe,tube,(2) channels, official or otherwise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "俳優",
        "Back": "actor,actress,player,performer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1212
    },
    {
        "Front": "パイロット",
        "Back": "pilot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "墓",
        "Back": "grave,tomb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1213
    },
    {
        "Front": "馬鹿",
        "Back": "fool,idiot,trivial matter,folly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1214
    },
    {
        "Front": "博士",
        "Back": "doctorate,PhD",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1215
    },
    {
        "Front": "計る",
        "Back": "to measure,to weigh,to survey",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1216
    },
    {
        "Front": "履く",
        "Back": "to wear,to put on (lower body)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1217
    },
    {
        "Front": "吐く",
        "Back": "(1) to breathe,(2) to tell (lies),(3) to vomit,to disgorge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1218
    },
    {
        "Front": "拍手",
        "Back": "clapping hands,applause",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1219
    },
    {
        "Front": "莫大",
        "Back": "enormous,vast",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1220
    },
    {
        "Front": "爆発",
        "Back": "explosion,detonation,eruption",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1221
    },
    {
        "Front": "博物館",
        "Back": "museum",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1222
    },
    {
        "Front": "激しい",
        "Back": "violent,vehement,intense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1223
    },
    {
        "Front": "はさみ",
        "Back": "scissors",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "破産",
        "Back": "(personal) bankruptcy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1224
    },
    {
        "Front": "端",
        "Back": "end (e.g. of street),edge,tip,margin,point",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1225
    },
    {
        "Front": "始まり",
        "Back": "origin,beginning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1226
    },
    {
        "Front": "パス",
        "Back": "path,pass (in games)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "外す",
        "Back": "to unfasten,to remove",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1227
    },
    {
        "Front": "パスポート",
        "Back": "passport",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "旗",
        "Back": "flag",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1228
    },
    {
        "Front": "肌",
        "Back": "skin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1229
    },
    {
        "Front": "裸",
        "Back": "naked,nude",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1230
    },
    {
        "Front": "畑",
        "Back": "field",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1231
    },
    {
        "Front": "二十",
        "Back": "20 years old,20th year",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1232
    },
    {
        "Front": "働き",
        "Back": "work,labor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1233
    },
    {
        "Front": "バッグ",
        "Back": "bag,bug",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "発見",
        "Back": "discovery,detection,finding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1234
    },
    {
        "Front": "発行",
        "Back": "issue (publications)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1235
    },
    {
        "Front": "発車",
        "Back": "departure of a vehicle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1236
    },
    {
        "Front": "罰する",
        "Back": "to punish,to penalize",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1237
    },
    {
        "Front": "発達",
        "Back": "development,growth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1238
    },
    {
        "Front": "ばったり",
        "Back": "with a clash (thud),with a bang,plump,flop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "発展",
        "Back": "development,growth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1239
    },
    {
        "Front": "発表",
        "Back": "announcement,publication",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1240
    },
    {
        "Front": "発明",
        "Back": "invention",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1241
    },
    {
        "Front": "話し合う",
        "Back": "to discuss,to talk together",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1242
    },
    {
        "Front": "離す",
        "Back": "to part,divide,separate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1243
    },
    {
        "Front": "放す",
        "Back": "to separate,to set free",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1244
    },
    {
        "Front": "離れる",
        "Back": "to be separated from,to leave,to go away,to be a long way off",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1245
    },
    {
        "Front": "羽",
        "Back": "counter for birds,counter for rabbits",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1246
    },
    {
        "Front": "幅",
        "Back": "width,breadth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1247
    },
    {
        "Front": "母親",
        "Back": "mother",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1248
    },
    {
        "Front": "省く",
        "Back": "to omit,to eliminate,to curtail,to economize",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1249
    },
    {
        "Front": "場面",
        "Back": "scene,setting (e.g. of novel)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1250
    },
    {
        "Front": "腹",
        "Back": "abdomen,belly,stomach",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1251
    },
    {
        "Front": "原",
        "Back": "field,plain,prairie,tundra,moor,wilderness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1252
    },
    {
        "Front": "針",
        "Back": "needle,hand (e.g. clock)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1253
    },
    {
        "Front": "張る",
        "Back": "to stick,to paste",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1254
    },
    {
        "Front": "番",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1255
    },
    {
        "Front": "バン",
        "Back": "bun,van (caravan),VAN (value-added network)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "範囲",
        "Back": "extent,scope,sphere,range",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1256
    },
    {
        "Front": "反抗",
        "Back": "opposition,resistance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1257
    },
    {
        "Front": "犯罪",
        "Back": "crime",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1258
    },
    {
        "Front": "ハンサム",
        "Back": "handsome",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "判断",
        "Back": "judgement,decision",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1259
    },
    {
        "Front": "犯人",
        "Back": "offender,criminal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1260
    },
    {
        "Front": "販売",
        "Back": "sale,selling,marketing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1261
    },
    {
        "Front": "灯",
        "Back": "light",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1262
    },
    {
        "Front": "ビール",
        "Back": "beer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "被害",
        "Back": "damage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1263
    },
    {
        "Front": "比較",
        "Back": "comparison",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1264
    },
    {
        "Front": "轢く",
        "Back": "to run somebody over (with vehicle),to knock someone down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1265
    },
    {
        "Front": "ピクニック",
        "Back": "picnic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "悲劇",
        "Back": "tragedy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1266
    },
    {
        "Front": "飛行",
        "Back": "aviation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1267
    },
    {
        "Front": "膝",
        "Back": "knee,lap",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1268
    },
    {
        "Front": "非常",
        "Back": "emergency,extraordinary,unusual",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1269
    },
    {
        "Front": "美人",
        "Back": "beautiful person (woman)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1270
    },
    {
        "Front": "びっくり",
        "Back": "be surprised,be amazed,be frightened,astonishment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "日付",
        "Back": "date,dating",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1271
    },
    {
        "Front": "必死",
        "Back": "inevitable death,desperation,frantic,inevitable result",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1272
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぴったり",
        "Back": "exactly,neatly,sharp",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "引っ張る",
        "Back": "(1) to pull,to draw,to stretch,to drag,(2) to pull the ball (baseball)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1273
    },
    {
        "Front": "否定",
        "Back": "negation,denial,repudiation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1274
    },
    {
        "Front": "ビデオ",
        "Back": "video",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "一言",
        "Back": "single word",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1275
    },
    {
        "Front": "人込み",
        "Back": "crowd of people",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1276
    },
    {
        "Front": "等しい",
        "Back": "equal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1277
    },
    {
        "Front": "独り",
        "Back": "alone,unmarried",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1278
    },
    {
        "Front": "一人一人",
        "Back": "one by one,each,one at a time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1279
    },
    {
        "Front": "批判",
        "Back": "criticism,judgement,comment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1280
    },
    {
        "Front": "批評",
        "Back": "criticism,review,commentary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1281
    },
    {
        "Front": "秘密",
        "Back": "secret,secrecy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1282
    },
    {
        "Front": "微妙",
        "Back": "delicate,subtle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1283
    },
    {
        "Front": "紐",
        "Back": "(1) string,cord,(2) pimp",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1284
    },
    {
        "Front": "費用",
        "Back": "cost,expense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1285
    },
    {
        "Front": "表",
        "Back": "table (e.g. Tab 1),chart,list",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1286
    },
    {
        "Front": "秒",
        "Back": "second (60th min)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1287
    },
    {
        "Front": "評価",
        "Back": "valuation,estimation,assessment,evaluation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1288
    },
    {
        "Front": "表現",
        "Back": "expression,presentation,representation (math)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1289
    },
    {
        "Front": "表情",
        "Back": "facial expression",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1290
    },
    {
        "Front": "平等",
        "Back": "equality (a),impartiality,evenness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1291
    },
    {
        "Front": "評判",
        "Back": "fame,reputation,popularity,arrant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1292
    },
    {
        "Front": "表面",
        "Back": "surface,outside,face,appearance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1293
    },
    {
        "Front": "広がる",
        "Back": "to spread (out),to extend,to stretch,to reach to,to get around",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1294
    },
    {
        "Front": "瓶",
        "Back": "bottle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1295
    },
    {
        "Front": "便",
        "Back": "way,means",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1296
    },
    {
        "Front": "ピン",
        "Back": "pin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "不",
        "Back": "un,non,negative prefix",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1297
    },
    {
        "Front": "無",
        "Back": "nothing,naught,nil,zero",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1298
    },
    {
        "Front": "分",
        "Back": "dividing,part",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1299
    },
    {
        "Front": "不安",
        "Back": "anxiety,uneasiness,insecurity,suspense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1300
    },
    {
        "Front": "風景",
        "Back": "scenery",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1301
    },
    {
        "Front": "夫婦",
        "Back": "married couple,husband and wife",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1302
    },
    {
        "Front": "笛",
        "Back": "flute,pipe",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1303
    },
    {
        "Front": "不可",
        "Back": "wrong,bad,improper,unjustifiable,inadvisable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1304
    },
    {
        "Front": "武器",
        "Back": "weapon,arms,ordinance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1305
    },
    {
        "Front": "服装",
        "Back": "garments",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1306
    },
    {
        "Front": "含む",
        "Back": "to hold in the mouth,to bear in mind",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1307
    },
    {
        "Front": "袋",
        "Back": "bag,sack",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1308
    },
    {
        "Front": "不幸",
        "Back": "unhappiness,sorrow,misfortune,disaster,accident,death",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1309
    },
    {
        "Front": "節",
        "Back": "tune,tone,knot,knob,point",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1310
    },
    {
        "Front": "無事",
        "Back": "safety,peace,quietness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1311
    },
    {
        "Front": "不思議",
        "Back": "mystery,curiosity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1312
    },
    {
        "Front": "不自由",
        "Back": "discomfort,disability,inconvenience,destitution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1313
    },
    {
        "Front": "夫人",
        "Back": "wife,Mrs,madam",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1314
    },
    {
        "Front": "婦人",
        "Back": "woman,female",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1315
    },
    {
        "Front": "不正",
        "Back": "injustice,unfairness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1316
    },
    {
        "Front": "防ぐ",
        "Back": "to defend (against),to protect,to prevent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1317
    },
    {
        "Front": "不足",
        "Back": "insufficiency,shortage,deficiency,lack,dearth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1318
    },
    {
        "Front": "舞台",
        "Back": "stage (theatre)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1319
    },
    {
        "Front": "双子",
        "Back": "twins,a twin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1320
    },
    {
        "Front": "再び",
        "Back": "again,once more,a second time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1321
    },
    {
        "Front": "普段",
        "Back": "usually,habitually,ordinarily,always",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1322
    },
    {
        "Front": "縁",
        "Back": "a means, e.g. of living",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1323
    },
    {
        "Front": "打つ",
        "Back": "to hit,to strike",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1324
    },
    {
        "Front": "物価",
        "Back": "prices of commodities,prices (in general)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1325
    },
    {
        "Front": "物質",
        "Back": "material,substance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1326
    },
    {
        "Front": "物理",
        "Back": "physics",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1327
    },
    {
        "Front": "筆",
        "Back": "writing brush",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1328
    },
    {
        "Front": "ふと",
        "Back": "suddenly,casually,accidentally,incidentally,unexpectedly,unintentionally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "船",
        "Back": "ship,boat,watercraft,shipping,vessel,steamship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1330
    },
    {
        "Front": "部分",
        "Back": "portion,section,part",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1331
    },
    {
        "Front": "不平",
        "Back": "complaint,discontent,dissatisfaction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1332
    },
    {
        "Front": "不満",
        "Back": "dissatisfaction,displeasure,discontent,complaints,unhappiness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1333
    },
    {
        "Front": "プラス",
        "Back": "plus",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "プラン",
        "Back": "plan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "不利",
        "Back": "disadvantage,handicap,unfavorable,drawback",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1334
    },
    {
        "Front": "振る",
        "Back": "(1) to wave,to shake,to swing,(2) to sprinkle,(3) to cast (actor),to allocate (work)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1335
    },
    {
        "Front": "震える",
        "Back": "to shiver,to shake,to quake",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1336
    },
    {
        "Front": "ブレーキ",
        "Back": "a brake",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "触れる",
        "Back": "to touch,to be touched,to touch on a subject,to feel,to violate (law, copyright, etc.),to perceive,t",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1337
    },
    {
        "Front": "風呂",
        "Back": "bath",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1338
    },
    {
        "Front": "プロ",
        "Back": "professional",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "文",
        "Back": "sentence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1339
    },
    {
        "Front": "雰囲気",
        "Back": "atmosphere (e.g. musical),mood,ambience",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1340
    },
    {
        "Front": "分析",
        "Back": "analysis",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1341
    },
    {
        "Front": "文明",
        "Back": "civilization,culture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1342
    },
    {
        "Front": "分野",
        "Back": "field,sphere,realm,division,branch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1343
    },
    {
        "Front": "塀",
        "Back": "wall,fence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1344
    },
    {
        "Front": "平均",
        "Back": "equilibrium,balance,average,mean",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1345
    },
    {
        "Front": "平和",
        "Back": "peace,harmony",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1346
    },
    {
        "Front": "別に",
        "Back": "(not) particularly,nothing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1347
    },
    {
        "Front": "減らす",
        "Back": "to abate,to decrease,to diminish,to shorten",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1348
    },
    {
        "Front": "減る",
        "Back": "to decrease (in size or number),to diminish,to abate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1349
    },
    {
        "Front": "ベルト",
        "Back": "Belt for western clothes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "変化",
        "Back": "goblin,ghost,apparition,bugbear",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1350
    },
    {
        "Front": "ペンキ",
        "Back": "(n) paint (nl: pek)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "勉強",
        "Back": "study,diligence,discount,reduction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1351
    },
    {
        "Front": "変更",
        "Back": "change,modification,alteration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1352
    },
    {
        "Front": "ベンチ",
        "Back": "bench",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "弁当",
        "Back": "box lunch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1353
    },
    {
        "Front": "方",
        "Back": "side",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1354
    },
    {
        "Front": "法",
        "Back": "Act (law: the X Act)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1355
    },
    {
        "Front": "棒",
        "Back": "pole,rod,stick",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1356
    },
    {
        "Front": "冒険",
        "Back": "risk,venture,adventure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1357
    },
    {
        "Front": "方向",
        "Back": "direction,course,way",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1358
    },
    {
        "Front": "報告",
        "Back": "report,information",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1359
    },
    {
        "Front": "宝石",
        "Back": "gem,jewel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1360
    },
    {
        "Front": "放送",
        "Back": "broadcast,broadcasting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1361
    },
    {
        "Front": "豊富",
        "Back": "abundance,wealth,plenty,bounty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1362
    },
    {
        "Front": "方法",
        "Back": "method,manner,way,means,technique",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1363
    },
    {
        "Front": "訪問",
        "Back": "call,visit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1364
    },
    {
        "Front": "吠える",
        "Back": "to bark,to bay,to howl,to bellow,to roar,to cry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1365
    },
    {
        "Front": "ボーイ",
        "Back": "boy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ボート",
        "Back": "rowing boat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ホーム",
        "Back": "(1) platform,(2) home",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ボール",
        "Back": "ball,bowl",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "外",
        "Back": "other place,the rest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1366
    },
    {
        "Front": "誇り",
        "Back": "pride",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1367
    },
    {
        "Front": "埃",
        "Back": "dust",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1368
    },
    {
        "Front": "保証",
        "Back": "guarantee,security,assurance,pledge,warranty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1369
    },
    {
        "Front": "保存",
        "Back": "preservation,conservation,storage,maintenance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1370
    },
    {
        "Front": "程",
        "Back": "degree,extent,bounds,limit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1371
    },
    {
        "Front": "歩道",
        "Back": "footpath,walkway,sidewalk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1372
    },
    {
        "Front": "仏",
        "Back": "Buddha,merciful person,Buddhist image,the dead",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1373
    },
    {
        "Front": "骨",
        "Back": "bone",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1374
    },
    {
        "Front": "炎",
        "Back": "flame",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1375
    },
    {
        "Front": "頬",
        "Back": "cheek (of face)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1376
    },
    {
        "Front": "ほぼ",
        "Back": "almost,roughly,approximately",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "微笑む",
        "Back": "to smile",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1377
    },
    {
        "Front": "褒める",
        "Back": "to praise,to admire,to speak well",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1378
    },
    {
        "Front": "濠",
        "Back": "moat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1379
    },
    {
        "Front": "本当",
        "Back": "truth,reality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1380
    },
    {
        "Front": "本人",
        "Back": "the person himself",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1381
    },
    {
        "Front": "本物",
        "Back": "genuine article",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1382
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぼんやり",
        "Back": "absent-minded,block-head,dim,faint,vague",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "間",
        "Back": "space,room,time,pause",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1383
    },
    {
        "Front": "まあ",
        "Back": "(female) you might say",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "マーケット",
        "Back": "market",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "マイク",
        "Back": "mike",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "迷子",
        "Back": "lost (stray) child",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1384
    },
    {
        "Front": "任せる",
        "Back": "to entrust to another,to leave to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1385
    },
    {
        "Front": "幕",
        "Back": "curtain,bunting,act (in play)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1386
    },
    {
        "Front": "負け",
        "Back": "defeat,loss,losing (a game)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1387
    },
    {
        "Front": "孫",
        "Back": "grandchild",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1388
    },
    {
        "Front": "まさか",
        "Back": "by no means",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "まさに",
        "Back": "correctly,surely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "真面目",
        "Back": "diligent,serious,honest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1389
    },
    {
        "Front": "増す",
        "Back": "to increase,to grow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1390
    },
    {
        "Front": "先ず",
        "Back": "first (of all),to start with,about,almost,hardly (with neg. verb)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1391
    },
    {
        "Front": "貧しい",
        "Back": "poor,needy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1392
    },
    {
        "Front": "マスター",
        "Back": "proprietor,manager,barowner,master (e.g. arts, science)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ますます",
        "Back": "increasingly,more and more",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "又",
        "Back": "again,and",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1393
    },
    {
        "Front": "未だ",
        "Back": "yet,still,more,besides",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1394
    },
    {
        "Front": "街",
        "Back": "(1) town,(2) street,road",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1395
    },
    {
        "Front": "間違い",
        "Back": "mistake",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1396
    },
    {
        "Front": "松",
        "Back": "(1) pine tree,(2) highest (of a three-tier ranking system)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1397
    },
    {
        "Front": "真っ赤",
        "Back": "deep red,flushed (of face)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1398
    },
    {
        "Front": "真っ直ぐ",
        "Back": "straight (ahead),direct,upright",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1399
    },
    {
        "Front": "全く",
        "Back": "really,truly,entirely,completely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1400
    },
    {
        "Front": "祭",
        "Back": "festival,feast",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1401
    },
    {
        "Front": "学ぶ",
        "Back": "to study (in depth),to learn,to take lessons in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1402
    },
    {
        "Front": "真似",
        "Back": "mimicry,imitation,behavior,pretense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1403
    },
    {
        "Front": "招く",
        "Back": "to invite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1404
    },
    {
        "Front": "ママ",
        "Back": "Mama",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "豆",
        "Back": "beans,peas",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1405
    },
    {
        "Front": "守る",
        "Back": "to protect,to obey,to guard,to abide (by the rules)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1406
    },
    {
        "Front": "丸",
        "Back": "circle,full (month),perfection,purity,suffix for ship names",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1407
    },
    {
        "Front": "丸い",
        "Back": "round,circular,spherical",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1408
    },
    {
        "Front": "まるで",
        "Back": "quite,entirely,completely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "回す",
        "Back": "to turn,to revolve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1409
    },
    {
        "Front": "回り",
        "Back": "circumference,surroundings,circulation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1410
    },
    {
        "Front": "万一",
        "Back": "by some chance,by some possibility,if by any chance,10E4:1 odds",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1411
    },
    {
        "Front": "満足",
        "Back": "satisfaction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1412
    },
    {
        "Front": "身",
        "Back": "body,main part,oneself,sword",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1413
    },
    {
        "Front": "実",
        "Back": "fruit,nut,seed,content,good result",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1414
    },
    {
        "Front": "見送り",
        "Back": "seeing one off,farewell,escort",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1415
    },
    {
        "Front": "味方",
        "Back": "friend,ally,supporter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1416
    },
    {
        "Front": "見事",
        "Back": "splendid,magnificent,beautiful,admirable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1417
    },
    {
        "Front": "ミス",
        "Back": "miss (mistake, error, failure),Miss",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "満ちる",
        "Back": "to be full,to rise (tide),to mature,to expire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1418
    },
    {
        "Front": "密",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1419
    },
    {
        "Front": "認める",
        "Back": "to recognize,to appreciate,to approve,to admit,to notice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1420
    },
    {
        "Front": "皆",
        "Back": "all,everyone,everybody",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1421
    },
    {
        "Front": "見舞い",
        "Back": "enquiry,expression of sympathy,expression of concern",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1422
    },
    {
        "Front": "土産",
        "Back": "present,souvenir",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1423
    },
    {
        "Front": "都",
        "Back": "capital",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1424
    },
    {
        "Front": "妙",
        "Back": "strange,unusual",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1425
    },
    {
        "Front": "明後日",
        "Back": "day after tomorrow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1426
    },
    {
        "Front": "未来",
        "Back": "future (life, tense)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1427
    },
    {
        "Front": "魅力",
        "Back": "charm,fascination,glamour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1428
    },
    {
        "Front": "見る",
        "Back": "to see,to watch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1429
    },
    {
        "Front": "ミルク",
        "Back": "milk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "向かい",
        "Back": "facing,opposite,across the street,other side",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1430
    },
    {
        "Front": "迎え",
        "Back": "meeting,person sent to pick up an arrival",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1431
    },
    {
        "Front": "向く",
        "Back": "to face",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1432
    },
    {
        "Front": "向ける",
        "Back": "to turn towards,to point",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1433
    },
    {
        "Front": "無視",
        "Back": "disregard,ignore",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1434
    },
    {
        "Front": "虫歯",
        "Back": "cavity,tooth decay,decayed tooth,caries",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1435
    },
    {
        "Front": "寧ろ",
        "Back": "rather,better,instead",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1436
    },
    {
        "Front": "結ぶ",
        "Back": "to tie,to bind,to link",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1437
    },
    {
        "Front": "無駄",
        "Back": "futility,uselessness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1438
    },
    {
        "Front": "夢中",
        "Back": "daze,(in a) trance,ecstasy,delirium,engrossment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1439
    },
    {
        "Front": "胸",
        "Back": "breast,chest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1440
    },
    {
        "Front": "無料",
        "Back": "free,no charge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1441
    },
    {
        "Front": "芽",
        "Back": "sprout",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1442
    },
    {
        "Front": "明確",
        "Back": "clear up,clarify,define",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1443
    },
    {
        "Front": "命じる",
        "Back": "to order,to command,to appoint",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1444
    },
    {
        "Front": "名人",
        "Back": "master,expert",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1445
    },
    {
        "Front": "命令",
        "Back": "order,command,decree,directive,(software) instruction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1446
    },
    {
        "Front": "迷惑",
        "Back": "trouble,bother,annoyance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1447
    },
    {
        "Front": "飯",
        "Back": "(sl) meals,food",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1448
    },
    {
        "Front": "滅多に",
        "Back": "rarely (with neg. verb),seldom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1449
    },
    {
        "Front": "メモ",
        "Back": "memorandum",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "面",
        "Back": "face,mug,surface,facial features,mask,face guard,side or facet,corner,page",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1450
    },
    {
        "Front": "綿",
        "Back": "cotton,padding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1451
    },
    {
        "Front": "免許",
        "Back": "license,permit,licence,certificate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1452
    },
    {
        "Front": "面倒",
        "Back": "trouble,difficulty,care,attention",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1453
    },
    {
        "Front": "メンバー",
        "Back": "member",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "申し込む",
        "Back": "to apply for,to make an application",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1454
    },
    {
        "Front": "申し訳",
        "Back": "apology,excuse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1455
    },
    {
        "Front": "毛布",
        "Back": "blanket",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1456
    },
    {
        "Front": "燃える",
        "Back": "to burn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1457
    },
    {
        "Front": "目的",
        "Back": "purpose,goal,aim,objective,intention",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1458
    },
    {
        "Front": "目標",
        "Back": "mark,objective,target",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1459
    },
    {
        "Front": "木曜",
        "Back": "Thursday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1460
    },
    {
        "Front": "文字",
        "Back": "letter (of alphabet),character",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1461
    },
    {
        "Front": "もしも",
        "Back": "if",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "持ち上げる",
        "Back": "to raise,to lift up,to flatter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1462
    },
    {
        "Front": "用いる",
        "Back": "to use,to make use of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1463
    },
    {
        "Front": "勿論",
        "Back": "of course,certainly,naturally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1464
    },
    {
        "Front": "最も",
        "Back": "most,extremely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1465
    },
    {
        "Front": "尤も",
        "Back": "quite right,plausible,natural,but then,although",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1466
    },
    {
        "Front": "元",
        "Back": "(1) origin,original,(2) former",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1467
    },
    {
        "Front": "基",
        "Back": "basis",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1468
    },
    {
        "Front": "素",
        "Back": "prime",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1469
    },
    {
        "Front": "戻す",
        "Back": "to restore,to put back,to return",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1470
    },
    {
        "Front": "基づく",
        "Back": "to be grounded on,to be based on,to be due to,to originate from",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1471
    },
    {
        "Front": "求める",
        "Back": "to seek,to request,to demand,to want,to wish for,to search for,to pursue (pleasure),to hunt (a job),",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1472
    },
    {
        "Front": "者",
        "Back": "person",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1473
    },
    {
        "Front": "物音",
        "Back": "sounds",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1474
    },
    {
        "Front": "物語",
        "Back": "tale,story,legend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1475
    },
    {
        "Front": "物事",
        "Back": "things,everything",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1476
    },
    {
        "Front": "模様",
        "Back": "pattern,figure,design",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1477
    },
    {
        "Front": "貰う",
        "Back": "to receive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1478
    },
    {
        "Front": "文句",
        "Back": "phrase,complaint",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1479
    },
    {
        "Front": "やがて",
        "Back": "before long,soon,at length",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "役",
        "Back": "use,service,role,position",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1480
    },
    {
        "Front": "約",
        "Back": "approximately,about,some",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1481
    },
    {
        "Front": "訳",
        "Back": "meaning,reason,circumstances,can be deduced,situation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1482
    },
    {
        "Front": "役割",
        "Back": "part,assigning (allotment of) parts,role,duties",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1483
    },
    {
        "Front": "家賃",
        "Back": "rent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1484
    },
    {
        "Front": "厄介",
        "Back": "trouble,burden,care,bother",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1485
    },
    {
        "Front": "宿",
        "Back": "inn,lodging",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1486
    },
    {
        "Front": "雇う",
        "Back": "to employ,to hire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1487
    },
    {
        "Front": "屋根",
        "Back": "roof",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1488
    },
    {
        "Front": "やはり",
        "Back": "also,as I thought,still,in spite of,absolutely,of course",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "破る",
        "Back": "to tear,to violate,to defeat,to smash,to destroy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1489
    },
    {
        "Front": "辞める",
        "Back": "to retire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1490
    },
    {
        "Front": "やや",
        "Back": "a little,partially,somewhat,a short time,a while",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "唯一",
        "Back": "only,sole,unique",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1491
    },
    {
        "Front": "勇気",
        "Back": "courage,bravery,valour,nerve,boldness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1492
    },
    {
        "Front": "有効",
        "Back": "validity,availability,effectiveness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1493
    },
    {
        "Front": "優秀",
        "Back": "superiority,excellence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1494
    },
    {
        "Front": "優勝",
        "Back": "overall victory,championship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1495
    },
    {
        "Front": "友情",
        "Back": "friendship,fellowship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1496
    },
    {
        "Front": "友人",
        "Back": "friend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1497
    },
    {
        "Front": "有能",
        "Back": "able,capable,efficient,skill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1498
    },
    {
        "Front": "郵便",
        "Back": "mail,postal service",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1499
    },
    {
        "Front": "夕べ",
        "Back": "evening",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1500
    },
    {
        "Front": "ユーモア",
        "Back": "humor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "有利",
        "Back": "advantageous,better,profitable,lucrative",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1501
    },
    {
        "Front": "床",
        "Back": "floor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1502
    },
    {
        "Front": "愉快",
        "Back": "pleasant,happy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1503
    },
    {
        "Front": "輸出",
        "Back": "export",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1504
    },
    {
        "Front": "譲る",
        "Back": "to turn over,to assign,to hand over",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1505
    },
    {
        "Front": "豊か",
        "Back": "abundant,wealthy,plentiful,rich",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1506
    },
    {
        "Front": "ゆっくり",
        "Back": "slowly,at ease",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "輸入",
        "Back": "importation,import,introduction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1507
    },
    {
        "Front": "許す",
        "Back": "to permit,to allow,to approve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1508
    },
    {
        "Front": "夜",
        "Back": "evening,night",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1509
    },
    {
        "Front": "夜明け",
        "Back": "dawn,daybreak",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1510
    },
    {
        "Front": "様",
        "Back": "way,manner,kind",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1511
    },
    {
        "Front": "酔う",
        "Back": "to get drunk,to become intoxicated",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1512
    },
    {
        "Front": "容易",
        "Back": "easy,simple,plain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1513
    },
    {
        "Front": "陽気",
        "Back": "season,weather,cheerfulness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1514
    },
    {
        "Front": "要求",
        "Back": "request,demand,requisition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1515
    },
    {
        "Front": "用心",
        "Back": "care,precaution,guarding,caution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1516
    },
    {
        "Front": "様子",
        "Back": "aspect,state,appearance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1517
    },
    {
        "Front": "要するに",
        "Back": "in a word,after all,the point is ..,in short ..",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1518
    },
    {
        "Front": "要素",
        "Back": "element",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1519
    },
    {
        "Front": "要点",
        "Back": "gist,main point",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1520
    },
    {
        "Front": "曜日",
        "Back": "day of the week",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1521
    },
    {
        "Front": "ヨーロッパ",
        "Back": "Europe",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "予期",
        "Back": "expectation,assume will happen,forecast",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1522
    },
    {
        "Front": "横切る",
        "Back": "to cross (e.g. arms),to traverse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1523
    },
    {
        "Front": "予算",
        "Back": "estimate,budget",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1524
    },
    {
        "Front": "止す",
        "Back": "to cease,to abolish,to resign,to give up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1525
    },
    {
        "Front": "予測",
        "Back": "prediction,estimation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1526
    },
    {
        "Front": "ヨット",
        "Back": "yacht",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "夜中",
        "Back": "midnight,dead of night",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1527
    },
    {
        "Front": "世の中",
        "Back": "society,the world,the times",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1528
    },
    {
        "Front": "余分",
        "Back": "extra,excess,surplus",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1529
    },
    {
        "Front": "予報",
        "Back": "forecast,prediction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1530
    },
    {
        "Front": "予防",
        "Back": "prevention,precaution,protection against",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1531
    },
    {
        "Front": "読み",
        "Back": "reading",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1532
    },
    {
        "Front": "嫁",
        "Back": "bride,daughter-in-law",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1533
    },
    {
        "Front": "余裕",
        "Back": "surplus,composure,margin,room,time,allowance,scope,rope",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1534
    },
    {
        "Front": "より",
        "Back": "twist,ply",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "よると",
        "Back": "according to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "喜び",
        "Back": "(a) joy,(a) delight,rapture,pleasure,gratification,rejoicing,congratulations,felicitations",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1535
    },
    {
        "Front": "宜しい",
        "Back": "(hon) good,OK,all right,fine,very well,will do,may,can",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1536
    },
    {
        "Front": "よろしく",
        "Back": "well,properly,suitably,best regards,please remember me",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "来",
        "Back": ",for (10 days),next (year)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1538
    },
    {
        "Front": "ライター",
        "Back": "lighter,rider,writer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "楽",
        "Back": "comfort,ease",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1539
    },
    {
        "Front": "ラケット",
        "Back": "paddle,racket",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "利益",
        "Back": "profits,gains,(political, economic) interest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1540
    },
    {
        "Front": "理解",
        "Back": "understanding,comprehension",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1541
    },
    {
        "Front": "陸",
        "Back": "six (used in legal documents)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1542
    },
    {
        "Front": "利口",
        "Back": "clever,shrewd,bright,sharp,wise,intelligent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1543
    },
    {
        "Front": "離婚",
        "Back": "divorce",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1544
    },
    {
        "Front": "理想",
        "Back": "ideal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1545
    },
    {
        "Front": "率",
        "Back": "rate,ratio,proportion,percentage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1546
    },
    {
        "Front": "立派",
        "Back": "splendid,fine,handsome,elegant,imposing,prominent,legal,legitimate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1547
    },
    {
        "Front": "留学",
        "Back": "studying abroad",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1548
    },
    {
        "Front": "流行",
        "Back": "fashionable,fad,in vogue,prevailing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1549
    },
    {
        "Front": "量",
        "Back": "quantity,amount,volume,portion (of food)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1550
    },
    {
        "Front": "両替",
        "Back": "change,money exchange",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1551
    },
    {
        "Front": "料金",
        "Back": "fee,charge,fare",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1552
    },
    {
        "Front": "例",
        "Back": "instance,example,case",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1553
    },
    {
        "Front": "礼",
        "Back": "expression of gratitude",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1554
    },
    {
        "Front": "礼儀",
        "Back": "manners,courtesy,etiquette",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1555
    },
    {
        "Front": "冷静",
        "Back": "calm,composure,coolness,serenity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1556
    },
    {
        "Front": "列",
        "Back": "queue,line,row",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1557
    },
    {
        "Front": "列車",
        "Back": "train (ordinary)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1558
    },
    {
        "Front": "レポート",
        "Back": "report,paper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "練習",
        "Back": "practice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1559
    },
    {
        "Front": "連想",
        "Back": "association (of ideas),suggestion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1560
    },
    {
        "Front": "連続",
        "Back": "serial,consecutive,continuity,continuing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1561
    },
    {
        "Front": "老人",
        "Back": "the aged,old person",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1562
    },
    {
        "Front": "労働",
        "Back": "manual labor,toil,work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1563
    },
    {
        "Front": "ロケット",
        "Back": "locket,rocket",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "論じる",
        "Back": "to argue,to discuss,to debate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1564
    },
    {
        "Front": "論争",
        "Back": "controversy,dispute",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1565
    },
    {
        "Front": "論文",
        "Back": "thesis,essay,treatise,paper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1566
    },
    {
        "Front": "輪",
        "Back": "ring,hoop,circle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1567
    },
    {
        "Front": "ワイン",
        "Back": "wine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "わがまま",
        "Back": "selfishness,egoism,wilfulness,disobedience,whim",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "別れ",
        "Back": "parting,separation,farewell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1568
    },
    {
        "Front": "脇",
        "Back": "side",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1569
    },
    {
        "Front": "分ける",
        "Back": "to divide,to separate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1570
    },
    {
        "Front": "わざと",
        "Back": "on purpose",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "僅か",
        "Back": "only,merely,a little,small quantity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1571
    },
    {
        "Front": "話題",
        "Back": "topic,subject",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1572
    },
    {
        "Front": "笑い",
        "Back": "laugh,laughter,smile",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1573
    },
    {
        "Front": "割る",
        "Back": "to divide,to cut,to break,to halve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1574
    },
    {
        "Front": "悪口",
        "Back": "abuse,insult,slander,evil speaking",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1575
    },
    {
        "Front": "我々",
        "Back": "we",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1576
    },
    {
        "Front": "湾",
        "Back": "bay,gulf,inlet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n3-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1577
    }
]